We in the building bro
Let's get it man everybody smash that like button
Share this video or this live stream if you can drop a comment when you get in the building
We cooking tonight bro
I got these pics I gotta give y'all
Then right after the pics we getting straight to the action
May may love
Last week I was impressed with my performance
But we still got to go
I'mma just put on my best performance in TKO debate series history
Telling y'all bro
Y'all know I don't give me saying shit
I been studied
I'm prepared
And I think there's no way out for Jay Chesna tonight
We got KQKC coming through the moderate to debate tonight
We got Dill Rice out coming through the judge to debate tonight
We got Get the Smoke coming through the judge to debate tonight
And my brother BFTV Fox is coming through to judge to debate tonight
I promise y'all I don't want to mix it bro
I just hope my brother Jay Chesna don't get star struck man
I hope you come prepared and ready to do your thing
Come with some good arguments bro
My shit through bro
Oh and we gonna try to get all our pics
We been on the road with the pics lately too
We gonna try to get all our pics right
It's tough this week
I'm picking some upsets this week so you know
If we right we make a bunch of money
If we wrong we lose
But I'm trying to be right
Cause I think the bookies got some shit wrong this week even
Get them lights up run them lights up drop a comment
Let me know you in here bro
Hey y'all know what's crazy
I'm undefeated
But I'm still hungry like I'm not undefeated
Like I still wanna strive for something like
I got something to prove to somebody
So I'm proving a point tonight dawg
I am that guy when it comes to this boxing talk shit bro
That's what we trying to prove tonight
But let me uh let me turn this camera off
Let me turn the camera off you know what I'm saying
Let me get that popping what's good
We got the red wine you know what I'm saying
We'll be starting the debate in about 55 minutes
But I gotta do these pics first
And we gotta get straight to the road calling straight to the pics
Cause we cramming it all in
The TKO prediction show in the TKO debate series
In one night and I'ma shine both of them
Yeah yeah yeah yeah both with the F both of them
You understand what I'm saying
Ray Patterson what's good
Roja what's up with it
Massa Musa lifestyle in the building what's good
with Opinion LDTV
Got his channel going shout out to Opinion Yalgo
Subscribe to his channel G Parker what's good
Daryl Deloach Thrill Hill
Flawless mentality in the building
Leon Robinson in the building what's up Leon
I'ma argue like you
They gonna ask me to join the damn law school Leon tonight
Leon they gonna ask me to join the law school tonight bro
They gonna be like hey man can you quit your job
You argue so well we need you to join the law school
We cooking tonight Josh Sanders what's good
Excuse me what's good with you Cassandra what's up with you
A BZ713 what's popping bro
PGH Big Dog in the building my beautiful
Beautiful beautiful wife in the building what's up baby
We got Omega Red and Slid up in here
OTB in the building what's good with the OTB
What's good with it
Lori Reed and came through she said who talking about tank
Who talking about tank somebody talking about tank
I'm who talking about tank
Y'all better not be tripping on tank
I got them Lori I got them tonight don't worry I got them
Easy work easy work
Oh we got James in the building what's good James
Who else we got man who else
Oh my brother Kyle from the boxing section
Sup bro shout out to Kyle y'all go subscribe to his channel
Check out what he got going on over there man
Check out what he got going on Todd Swindler what's good with you
What's popping with you Todd
Who else we got slid up through the back door
My brother right side is up in here what's up bro
What's up with it man shout out to you
Kwee Kwee the slid up in the building what's good with it
Kwee Kwee what's good with it
Kwee Kwee the right side be like
Man I'm gonna kill your ass fuck your whole family
You a punk ass nigga
Respectfully respect respectfully
Respectfully bro I mean no disrespect like bro stop
Stop putting respectfully at the end of your damn disrespect man
He be like he get mad about Earth's men's and Terrence Crawford
And shit he get mad about Earth's men's and Terrence Crawford
Be like man fuck both of them man
Fuck both of them fuck all of them fuck the PBC
I don't care about none of them forget all of them man
They all some hoes man
Respectfully of course respect like bro stop
Stop doing that shit man but let's get to it bro
We gotta get straight to the pics
Crush what's good with it crush we gotta get straight to the pics
Cause I got some food on my plate
I got some food on my plate that I gotta eat a little bit later man
I really really do I really really do bro
But let's just we going straight at it
We going straight at it cause I got so much to do man
I'm gonna start with we want an easy one
I'm looking for an easy one
Oh there go one
Frank Santas Carlos Negron
This is on the PBC card
Frank Santas is a minus three thousand favorite Carlos Negron
You right on time TJ Salute
Carlos Negron is plus one thousand
Negron out of Puerto Rico
Six foot six eighty three inch reach
Thirty four years old he's an orthodox fighter
Twenty five wins three losses
Twenty wins by way of knockout
And he's been knocked out three times
He got a nice left hook
He can't counter punch a little bit
He has some good power
But his gas tank look like it depletes very very fast
Smoke what up
And he's a plotter he ain't got no kind of foot movement
Frank Santas excellent movement for a heavyweight
Really good defense really elusive he's explosive
He's athletic he's powerful
Got really good boxing skills as Frank Santas
I question the aggression in the dog of Frank Santas
Like with his like he is too passive for my liking bro
Like Frank Santas will put your ass to sleep
He will put you to sleep if you allow him to
You know what I'm saying
So like after fighting guys like FAA a jogbook
Like Carlos Negron like this is a
This is a step down for FAA Frank should be able to take care of this
Very very good ancestral rage what up
So I want to see Frank Santas like winning
That's not enough for me bro I need you to step on the gas
I need you to put punches together
Running around the ring firing off a counter shot
Then running around the ring again bro throwing like 10 shots per round
Landing four of them like nah bro I can't
I can't with that Frank so I got Frank Santas to win
I need him to win by stoppage though
Carlos Negron is at a huge deficit in speed
He's at a huge deficit in boxing skills
He can't move with Frank Santas
Frank Santas ought to be able to walk him in the shit at will bro
He need to walk him in the shit at will for me to be impressed
And even then I'm gonna be like you just did that shit to somebody that
You know what I'm saying we knew you would do that too
But I got Frank Santas clearly in that fight
Let's keep this thing moving let's do
Let me see what's another one
What's another one because a lot of these is hard today bro
A lot of these is hard
Let's do another easy one
Let's do another easy one 40 people in the building to smash the like button
Devin Haney vs. George Camposso
We're gonna do another easy one real quick
Devin is a minus 900 favorite minus 190 for the decision
Plus 210 for the knockout
George Camposso is a plus 500 and plus 1200
For either a knockout or decision Camposso is 29 years old at
Australia 5 foot 9 68 inch reach Orthodox fighter 20 wins one loss
You know I mean one loss and he been and he got 10 knockout
This is for the 135 pound undisputed champion
Championship of the world I was reading TJ coming he got me all messed up man
Then you got Devin Haney 23 years old Orthodox fighter
5 foot 8 71 inch reach fighting out of Cali 28 wins no losses
He has 15 knockouts look man George Camposso he does have fast hands
Mr. Mechanical he got fast hands he's tough
But he got bad feeding he couldn't find his way on the inside against Devin Haney
In the first fight he had a huge huge huge huge problems breaking that distance
And that's because Devin got a great jab he got good distance control
He moves around the ring well very defensively responsible
Devin don't fight on the inside though when George Camposso did have moments where he got in
He just did the smart thing hurried up tied him up but Devin Haney good with his distance
One of the better jabs in the division and better jabs in boxing
And like we were talking about yesterday I want to see him turn it up a little bit
Now that you've shared the ring with Camposso's 12 rounds you know his speed
You know what he got you know what he don't got if your ring IQ is what we all believe
Devin Haney's ring IQ to be I ain't saying he got a knockout got to get the knockout even go for the knockout
But I do want to see that right hand war I want to see that lead right hand war I want to see more counter punching
I want to see you just making Camposso's miss I want to see you make him miss and make him pay a lot more
Pick him apart and if you stop him you stop him so I am looking for Devin Haney to win a wide wide wide unanimous decision
Teach what up somewhere along the lines of just like last time 10 rounds to 2, 11 rounds to 1
At worst 9 rounds to 3 but I don't think George Camposso has anything for Devin Haney
Because George Camposso can't successfully break the distance he's not powerful enough
His head movement isn't good enough he's not explosive enough to close the distance quickly
He doesn't have a good enough jab to out jab Devin Haney to find his way inside
He's just at a deficit and I think Devin Haney will win a wide unanimous decision again in that fight
Let's keep it moving though man let's keep it moving
Caleb Plant Anthony Dorell
Caleb Plant Anthony Dorell 12 round super middleweight fight
Caleb Plant is a minus 1000 favorite I think those odds are way too wide plus 160 to get the knockout
Minus 175 for the decision
Like I said 12 round super middleweight fight Dorell is a plus 600 plus 1000 to get the knockout
Sheena I see you teach I see you was good which I'll man salute everybody in the building
Please hit the like button as you come in
And he's a plus 1600 to get the decision is Anthony Dorell
Leon say he got plant Rojah says plant by split decision
Dorell is 34 wins 2 losses 2 draws Orthodox fighter 6 foot 2 74 and a half inch reach out of Michigan
37 years old 25 wins by way of knockout he been knocked out one time
Then you got Caleb plant 21 wins 1 loss 12 12 knockouts and he been knocked out one time
Obviously in his most recent fight against Canelo Alvarez Anthony Dorell is a gamer bro
He's a gamer you put him in there with Kyron Davis you put him there with Avenue Yieldrum he like
He looks suspect but you put him in there with David Benavidez he gonna fight his ass off he gonna compete
The higher the competition the more that he's at a deficit the more that he's considered a underdog
Then the dog comes out got a green so he got the rail you make some money plus 600
Put a hundred down you win 600 if you think he gonna get the decision plus 1600 put a hundred down you win 1600
Then you gonna get the knockout got a green plus 1000 put a hundred down you win 1000 so if you write you can make some money
But um Anthony Dorell does everything pretty good he's an absolute dog
The issue I see with him is that he just tries to block your shots when you start throwing a combination
He'll block your shots he doesn't really throw a lot in between shots
And he is there to kind of his feet on what they used to be so he's kind of stationary
An easy target when he goes into the high guard but he is durable he is somebody that can take a good shot
So he's gonna really test Kaler Plant it's a good first fight back for Kaler Plant
Kaler Plant has average power he's very athletic has fast hands
The shoulder roll does work well for him when he's not tired but he does have a gas tank issue
Kaler Plant can counter punch has a nice jab very fast but when that gas tank starts to pleading round six round seven round eight
He slows down because he is a fighter that depends on being quick being athletic relying on my head movement
I got my hands down I'm relying on my foot movement I'm relying on my reflexes
But when you get tired it's about your technique and it's about how much skills you have
And he does have good skills but he doesn't he's not fundamental with him
You know what I'm saying he relies a lot on his athleticism just Kaler Plant
Now for this fight I kind of alluded to it yesterday for Anthony DeRail to win he got to make it close early
He got him put down in Kaler Plant early invest to the body early
Understanding that the game plan needs to be to just keep the fight close and then try to turn up later on in the fight
When Kaler Plant gas tank starts to deplete when those reflexes aren't as fast when he can't move around the ring as much
That's what Canelo Alvarez was able to do
For Kaler Plant get off to a big lead you got to get yourself a cushion you got to know yourself as a fighter
You got to know that for some reason no matter how hard you train he never miss weight he always look like he in great shape
Something always seems to be missing on the back half of the fight when it comes to Kaler Plant
What's up Zach I see you bro something always seems to be missing with him bro
No matter what you say no matter what how hard he train the back half of the fight is his kryptonite
So you got to know that about yourself and he got to get off to a big lead
He needs to be winning this fight at minimum four rounds to two five rounds to one halfway through the fight
Outbox Anthony DeRail early get his confidence going make it a very uneventful fight early
Do not mix it up if he gets to mixing it up early it could spell trouble for him not to say he can't win that type of fight
We saw him do very well against Uskaktiki but he needs to get out to a early and turn this and get off to a good start early
and turn this into a boxing match does Kaler Plant so with all that being said I do think that Anthony DeRail
if this fight was two or three years ago if he was 34 35 years old I'd give him a better shot
but I can't get out of my mind how he looked against Kyron Davis and then after Kyron Davis they put him in there with Markas and then Hernandez who already had four losses
and he put he got a nice highlight reel knockout but I just think that Anthony DeRail the better part of his career is behind him
I think Kaler Plant's youth at 30 years old his freshness having some time out of the ring about a year
I think Kaler Plant's going to be the fresher fighter I think he does get off to that good start
I think he wins a competitive unanimous decision that doesn't get competitive until late
I think it's about eight rounds to four nine rounds to three in favor of Kaler Plant
I expect the scorecards to be like 116 and 112 where you can probably say Anthony DeRail probably won three of the last five rounds
you know something like that where he turned up late but Kaler Plant had built such a lead that he was able to you know just kind of coast to a victory
so I got Kaler Plant in that fight by unanimous decision
alright let's do a toss up fight let's do a toss up fight this fight will be in the afternoon this is going to be on D'Zone
Liam Parrow versus Brock Jarvis a lot of money to be made here if you can get this one right this is a 12 round super lightweight fight
they fighting at 140 pounds Liam Perot is a minus 220 Brock Jarvis is a plus 180
Liam Perot is 26 years old he's a Southpaw he's five foot eight and a half 71 inch reach fighting out of Australia
22 wins no losses with 13 wins by way of knockout
then you got Brock Jarvis five foot nine 68 and a half inch reach 24 years old fighting out of Australia as well
he's an orthodox fighter 20 wins no losses 18 wins by way of knockout
Liam Perot has good enough power to keep people off of him he has a nice one too
he's good when you allow him to box from a distance if you crowd him he likes to hold a lot
not to say that he can't fight inside because I have seen him throw hooks on the inside try to do some work on the inside
but he's much more comfortable when you when you allow him to to kind of have his distance and be able to just box you
he just he's somebody that does need a lot of space and his feet are slow but he knows how to move around the ring
so he's not athletic he ain't jumping back jumping forward pivoting off to the side pivoting off to the other side
he not doing all that but he knows he knows how to place his feet he knows how to how to get out of trouble
and he has a pretty good defense high guard but not not parrying not really a lot of head movement
but just a good solid fundamental fringe kind of world class fighter you know one of those guys at 140 that that probably won't ever be a champion
probably won't be a champion but he can go rounds with champions probably won't be a champion but if you are overrated prospect
if you somebody that is not world class what's up with the key then he can probably get you you know I'm saying but Liam Perry was a good fighter
then you got Brock Jarvis he's explosive and athletic he's come up a lot of weight classes in a short period of time
I saw TJ bring up that great point he started his career at a much lower weight class but he's been growing and growing and growing
and now he's making his debut at 140 he's really good inside with taking different angles pivoting here boom right hand to the body pivoting over there
boom left hand to the body high work rate will smother you very very quick and athletic and explosive
defense is lacking in his last fight his debut on the zone he got rocked he got hurt okay he recovered
he recovered but that fight could have possibly been stopped because he did look like he got knocked through the damn ropes I ain't gonna lie to y'all
at the very least they should have scored at a knockdown but hey man the zone the zone see some minimum the zone really want to push him
so that fight went on that was in the second round he ended up taking that fight back over and he ended up doing really really good work
and he got the stoppage I thought that he did have the dude hurt that he stopped but I thought the fight could have continued because Brock Jarvis was far more hurt
in the second round than the guy that he was fighting was hurt in the in the fifth round but he is looking to be inside with you he want to be head to head
chest to chest let's see who can be the better inside fighter but he's explosive raw powerful there's a reason he has a 90%
K O percentage so what is this fight gonna come down to it's the explosiveness in the athleticism and the inside fighting of Brock Jarvis versus the technical ability
in the skills and the better admit range of Liam Perrow so who do you think what it comes down to when you say who you picking who do you think is gonna have a fight fault on their turn
do you think that Brock Jarvis will find his way inside and be able to turn this into a a brawl or inside fight or do you think Liam Perrow will catch him coming in
use his jab keep him at a distance where he can out box him and out think him or can Brock Jarvis like I said turn this into a work a workman type of fight
where it's inside is they dogging it out for me for me bro like I want to pick I want to pick Brock Jarvis he's young and he's wrong he's athletic and so I'm gonna pick Brock Jarvis like I got Brock Jarvis in the fight
a lot of people are picking Liam Perrow but I just think Brock Jarvis gonna find his way inside and the guy that's training him I forget his name they say he's an Australian boxing legend
I admittedly don't know a lot about Australian boxing but I would think if somebody like that is training you they taking a liking to you they see something they see something in you
and so with that being said bro I just like Brock Jarvis style and I think Liam Perrow albeit a very good fighter I don't think he's good enough to keep somebody like Brock Jarvis who is more explosive who is more athletic to keep him from fighting his fight
I think Liam Perrow might start off being very being very you know in control of the fight but I think Brock Jarvis may just throw caution to the wind as a young fighter that never lost before he gonna come and he gonna try to do everything he can to make it a scrap
and if he finds his way inside and if it turns into a power punch and matchup he gonna most definitely have the advantage and so I'm going with Brock Jarvis I'm rolling with Brock bro
I'm going I'm rolling with Brock one Tyson Fury I appreciate that thank you so much I'm rolling with Brock in the fight I got Brock Jarvis by unanimous decision I could see a late stopper in here but I'm a give Perrow the respect of saying that he undefeated he gonna go to distance
but I think Brock Jarvis is gonna get the W in this fight let's go to Gary Antonio Russell versus Emmanuel Rodriguez this is another good this is another good one bro
Gary Antonio Russell is only a minus 220 favorite and Emmanuel Rodriguez is a plus 180 this is a 12 round band on weight fight they fought before but it had to be a no contest because they had a headbutton like the first and second round and then she got called a no contest so they running it back
Gary Antonio Russell is 29 years old South Park 5 foot 767 inch reach fighting out of the DMV 19 wins no losses 12 wins by way of knockout Emmanuel Rodriguez 30 years old out of Puerto Rico 5 foot 6 with a 66 and a half inch reach
Orthodox fighter 20 wins 2 losses with 13 wins by way of knockout and he's been knocked out one time y'all get the lights up as well please King D I see you salute everybody in the building we will be getting the debate started in about 35 minutes we running down these pics right now then we getting to the action man we're gonna see what it do you know I mean
but for me manual Rodriguez look man he is a good boxer he can counter punch well specifically with his right hand double zeroes what up he has good punch variation not a whole lot of lateral movement not a whole lot of slips not a whole lot of head movement
head is on the line but um he does need to bring his left hand up he need to bring his left hand up um I'm debating being boxing news me versus J chestnut Javante Davis of course Steve is and we starting in about 30 minutes man about to get it pop and D man junior what up um and so Emmanuel Rodriguez very good offensively very good offensively
defense is lacking defense is what got him stopped against monster anyway defense is um it is something that he needs to work on now he has another loss against Ray Martin Gaballo I thought he won that fight I thought he won that fight to be perfectly honest with y'all it was a competitive fight but I thought
Rodriguez did out box him but um he's a good boxer a really good test for Gary Antonio Russell a really really really good test for Gary Antonio Russell best dad ever said getting ready for another snooze fest Saturday night man don't do there like that you got so many other fights that you could watch man
but don't worry tonight or best dad ever I'm cooking I'm cooking tonight man we you know we rockin with tank we got a tank in Shakur debate tonight in about 30 minutes and I'm gonna do my thing bro
and yeah I'll make a say debate one side on the KO is talking starting 30 minutes I gotta do the I gotta do the pigs bro I gotta get through the pigs the fans corner what up man
um gotta get through the pigs everybody's out come in smash the like button the base starting 30 minutes we running down the weekly pigs right now um and so yeah for Gary Antonio Russell he can counter punch nice right hook all them Russell brothers but they right hooks nasty
all of them the right hooks from that self proposition nasty he's defensively responsible and he got dog in them bro they all got dog in them like he nasty and mean on the inside he nasty and mean on the inside he don't really move a whole lot he did have a knee injury in his last fight I think his knee is better he said he had a great
he's got a great knee injury in his last fight so we're gonna take him out on his word for that I think matching these two fighters up is a great matchup because if Gary Antonio Russell is who his fans think he is then he should be somebody like Emmanuel Rodriguez with all the
guys that Emmanuel Rodriguez has um defensively with Gary Antonio Russell's hand speed um I think the Gary Antonio Russell um should win this fight and so I'm gonna pick him to win this fight I got the favor in this and I think he'll win the decision um he does have power but I mean Emmanuel Rodriguez he only been stopped by months anyway the hardest punch in the division so somebody else
gonna have to do it for me to pick it like and put my money on it I think Gary Antonio Russell wins the decision I think it'll be a competitive fight I think she had eight rounds to four maybe even seven rounds to five but I think Gary Antonio Russell will win simply because
they'll probably be even in mid range they probably both had a moment set me a range but when um when they get in close I think the tenacity the aggressiveness the relentlessness and the dog of Gary Antonio Russell and his unwillingness to clench bro like he don't want to clench Emmanuel Rodriguez will welcome a clinch and while he clenching Gary Antonio
Russell to be scoring so I think that inside work will be the difference in the fight um and so I'm going with Gary Antonio Russell by decision eight rounds to four maybe even seven rounds to five one sixteen one twelve on a couple score cards maybe one fifteen one thirteen on
the other wouldn't even be surprised that a split decision depending upon what type of work the judges like more but I think Gary Antonio Russell will edge it out let's keep it going 88 people now in the building they seated it or 91 now y'all seated is getting closer to debate time and you're coming in
the beta starting in 30 minutes we can we got a few more picks we gotta do I see my daughter Jada in the building my daughter Nivy in the building Salute Sweeties we got a couple more picks we gotta do and then we are getting it popping bro just a few more picks and then we getting it
popping so y'all stay tuned because I'm putting on the show tonight bro let me see here um okay DJ Black Charm music what's up bro Salute to you smash the like button hundred people
in here seventy five likes smash the like button you write on time saying Louis we about to get it started the base starts in 30 minutes man now you good Dominic you good everybody good I know what y'all here for but you need to be here for the picks
cuz y'all see that prediction record we've been eating lately I ain't hold y'all we've been eating lately bro we've been eating lately but let's let's get to it so what we gotta live I got gotta do the wilder I got the ladies Michelle Rivera oh yeah I got the ladies I gotta do and I got these um I did all of these oh no I got the Maloney's I ain't did the Maloney's
damn I got a lot I got a lot I gotta do man oh let's go ahead and knock out the Maloney brothers man let's knock out the Maloney brothers picks man he said I'm trying to hit these pigs I got you but where you go there they go all right bet
I already did some of them I did Kayla plant King D I got Kayla plant I did um Frank Sanchez I got Frank Sanchez in that fight I did I just did the Gary Antonio King King D I got Gary Antonio and that the only one I did was um the auntie wilder and Hela and then I did um I haven't done the Michelle Rivera or the veto mill Nicky I'm doing those two fights to they kind of give me fights to
the coach she just say I got both Maloney brothers already already listen man we got Andrew Maloney versus Norbell told him in X 10 round super flyway fight they fighting at 115 pounds minus 225 for Maloney plus 185 for him in X Maloney is 31 years old orthodox fighter 55 foot 5 say I see you what's up
5 foot 5 with a 65 inch reach fighting out of Australia then you got Maloney is 24 wins two losses 16 wins by way of knockout you got him in as plus 185 as I said 5 foot 6 68 inch reach fighting out of Dominican Republic orthodox fighter 31 years old 31 wins nine losses six draws 16 wins by way of knockout and he's been knocked out four times I am not gonna lie to y'all
esmark so I need my brother and I need them for a landing competition we ain't even strong enough to win this cerengums I've gotta think about one more fighter I've got two brothers have one is better than one and the Winnie the Pooh
He's very good inside.
He's a busy fighter, moves well in the ring,
very compact, high guard.
He relies more on his feet for defense.
Ain't a whole lot of slips and pulling back
and rolling with shots.
He'll parry a little bit, but he's high guard
and using his feet for his defense,
but very good on the inside with his hooks
uppercuts on the inside.
Nice little one-two from distance.
His two losses came to Joshua Franco,
and y'all know Joshua Franco can really, really, really fight.
Nobel told him in there,
look, he leans heavy over his front foot.
He got okay power.
He got a high guard with no head movement.
Goes to the body very nice,
but he rarely throws in between your shots.
He's a your turn, my turn fighter,
so I'm going to go into my high guard
while you throwing your shit.
Then when you get done throwing your shit,
I'm going to throw my shit, then I'm going to go back
into my high guard. Very rarely, you know,
I'm going to get off the line, throw my right hand
while you throw your right hand.
That's why you throwing your shit.
He don't do a lot of that.
I'm surprised that they got this shit so close.
I think if Jimenez had a better jab,
I think if Jimenez didn't lean so heavy
over his front foot and wasn't so open for uppercuts,
if he was a better inside fighter
than I could see the eyes,
but in this one, I do not see it, bro.
I don't see it at all.
I got Andrew Maloney by a wide unanimous decision,
possibly even a knockout in this fight.
Stopping Nobel told Jimenez
if he really turned up on him,
and then you know if he get them hurt,
if he get them buzzed, they fighting in Australia.
They fighting in Australia.
And so if he get them hurt, get them buzzed,
you can't be surprised with an early stoppage
with the rev wave and that shit off earth.
You can't be surprised with that.
So I got Andrew Maloney.
I go to late stoppage,
about around eight, around nine,
around eight, around nine, we'll go with Maloney.
Jason Maloney,
our next fight,
we're going to go to the next fight
of the year.
Our next fight,
Jason Maloney versus
Nawakaphon
Khakakon
Oni shit.
Nawapaphon is what I'm going to call him out of Thailand.
This is a 12 round
band and weight fight.
They got Jason Maloney as a minus nine
hundred favorite.
They got Nawapaphon
as a plus five, 50 underdog.
Nawapaphon
is 31 years old out of Thailand.
Five foot five
orthodox fighter.
Jason Maloney is 31 years old also
out of Australia.
Orthodox fighter,
five foot five with a 65 inch
reach.
Jason Maloney
is 24 wins, two losses
with 19 knockouts
and he been knocked out one time.
Nawaphon
Rick Timbs what up
is 56 wins
one loss
one draw
with 46 wins coming by way of knockout
and he been knocked out one time
that was five and a half years ago
back in 2017
all the way down in Flyweight at 112 pounds.
Nawaphon is currently
on the 25th win street
and he's knocked out 18
of his last 20 opponents.
He is
been extremely active, had a lot of
fights in 2021 and been very busy
in 2022.
His one draw that he got
was the very first fight of his career.
So
his very first fight of his career he got a draw
then he won like 30 something
fights in a row.
Then he lost, then he won
like 20 fights in a row.
And his one draw came against
Rung Vesai.
He fought Rung Vesai in his very first professional fight
and fought him to a draw.
But this dude is patient.
He got fast hands
slow feet
but he cuts the ring off well.
His defense is questionable
and he got power
on top of power.
And his hands are fast.
And he's currently ranked number two
in the WBC.
Jason Maloney got good movement.
He got good power.
He like his brother
likes to fight on the inside.
He has a nice check left hook
and he can box.
Him and his brother have very similar styles.
Moving around the ring.
Not a whole lot of head movement.
Not great defense.
Just good movement. Good solid fundamental
boxers.
Jason Maloney didn't look too impressive
against Josh Greer.
He looked very impressive in his fight before that.
And he got beat by
what's the guy's name?
He wants to anyway knock him out.
So I'm telling you all right now
bro.
I don't know how these eyes are so god damn
wide.
TJ maybe you can help us out.
But I like
I watch now upon fight like
five or six times and make sure my eyes
wouldn't trip.
And for the life of me
I do not know why these eyes are so
wide bro.
I have no clue.
I try to find out on fight night.
But when I break down this fight
I'd be shocked
if Jason Maloney isn't on his back foot the entire night.
Trying to have lateral movement.
Trying to keep now upon from cutting off the ring.
And when now upon
it's cutting off the ring.
He'll throw to the body.
He'll throw to the body. He'll throw up top.
The power is real. The hand speed is real.
His only issue is foot speed.
But he does such a great job of being patient to where
he don't follow you around the ring.
And he'll say,
I'm going to take a slow step to you.
Run beside type of shit.
He ain't far the level of competition run beside fault.
That's not what I'm saying.
But that slow.
But the difference is he walked to you slow
like run beside to cut the ring off on you.
But the hands are much faster bro.
They much faster.
What up sis?
Sister in law in the building. What's good?
What's good with you?
What's good bro?
I got now upon bro.
I got now upon in this fight man.
I just think, here's why.
Because I think he going to have Jason Maloney on the run.
And I think Jason Maloney is going to get
tired from fighting off of his back foot the whole time.
And Jason Maloney has short ass arms.
So he got to walk through fire bro.
He got to come in through fire
to get to now upon.
And now upon is going to throw.
And this shit say that now upon is five five.
Bro I don't believe that shit.
He got to be at least about five seven bro.
And he fight tall.
And he parry away your shit man.
Now upon look like
he can fight. Yeah no curve ball.
None of that shit.
I got now upon bro.
I'm trusting my eyes. I could be dead ass wrong.
I could be dead ass wrong.
But my eyes tell me.
My eyes tell me that
now upon is going to be a problem.
I'm doing it TJ.
I'm doing it damn it.
I'm doing it now upon.
I think he might be some different TJ.
I think people are missing the boat on him.
He cause he goes to the body too.
That's the other thing that he does is a power puncher.
He throws to the body
to make you eventually have to stand still.
And if you have to stand still with him
your ass is in trouble.
And I know he fighting in Australia.
I know he fighting
a drink. I think it's cause they messed up.
Because they got his brother Andrew Maloney
as a minus two twenty five favorite.
And Norbolito Jimenez as a plus one
eighty five.
And in this fight with Jason Maloney
that I'm talking about right now.
They got him as a minus nine hundred.
And a plus five fifty for the duty fighting.
But the dude that Jason Maloney is fighting
is number two in the WBC and got a fifty six
and one record with forty six knockouts.
What a dude that Andrew Maloney is fighting
is thirty one and nine.
So I think they flip the odds bro.
I understand that TJ.
I understand that but Jason Maloney every time
he's fighting a good comp, like here's where I'm at TJ.
Joshua Greer has success
against Jason Maloney.
This guy is better than Joshua Greer bro.
He better than him.
Like way better than him bro.
Like I watched, I watched
Josh Greer have success
against his man Jason Maloney TJ.
I could be wrong bro.
I've been wrong before. You know what I mean?
I ain't above.
I've been right eighty six percent of the time
I've been wrong fourteen percent of the time.
This might fall until that fourteen percent.
But if I'm right, I'm gonna get that money.
I'm gonna get that money TJ.
I'm getting it.
I gotta get it.
You know what I mean?
Like and I hear what you're saying
about the level of competition that
that my boy, my boy now upon
I've been fighting but I mean other than
other than monster in a way
and you give them
Josh Greer or you give Jason Maloney
you give him Leonardo Baez who's a career
journeyman you know we don't think much of Leonardo
Baez who he fought.
Like who he been fighting?
He lost to Emmanuel Rodriguez
the guy that you know what I mean?
Like if Emmanuel Rodriguez
can fight with Jason Maloney and do something
with him bro I'd be like you can't tell me
that my boy
my boy now upon I can't do nothing with him
I'm going with the tie. I'm going with
Thailand bro.
I'm gonna tie. I got him. That's it.
I'm done talking about it. I'm gonna say
that he gets the stoppage.
I'm gonna say he gets the stoppage
late in the fight by wearing
Jason Maloney ass down bro.
So I'm going with now upon
Kakakon.
Now upon Kakakon.
Look out for him to possibly be
next in line of the great
Thai fighters man. He is coming
through the back door on your ass. So I did that fight.
Did that one. Did that one.
I did that one. Did that one.
I ain't did that one yet. Do you want to
say why are the Robin Helanias?
Yeah
drink. Drink. Look man if you miss it
if you
miss it drink
my fault. I say go watch him
fight first though. You gonna see some fast ass
hands some good ass power
he fight like Michael Myers in this
bro he you know who he fight like drink
I'm not even lying to y'all. Y'all go watch him fight.
He fight like David Benavidez bro.
He fight like David Benavidez.
Slow feet.
You don't know how he cut off the ring.
You don't know how he force and do's
to just sit down and fight with him.
But he make everybody sit down and fight with
that's how he fight and his hands are fast
and I mean
46 knockouts
and 56 wins is 46 knockouts
and 56 wins. Like I don't like
I don't know what y'all want me to do.
Okay.
So I'm picking
and if I'm right give me my flowers. If I'm wrong
don't show up. Alright that's how we come.
Well let's keep it going Wilder vs Helanias
12 round heavyweight fight.
Wilder
is a minus 800
minus 350 for the KO plus 550 for the decision
Helanias is a plus
500 plus 850 for the
KO plus 1200 for the decision
Helanias is an orthodox fighter
6 foot 6 79 inch reach out of Sweden
38 years old 31
wins 3 losses 20 wins by way of knockout
been knocked out twice. Wilder
is 6 foot 7
83 inch reach orthodox fighter out of Alabama
36 years old
42 wins 2 losses
1 draw 41 wins by way
of knockout and he's been stopped twice in his career.
Robert Helanias has a nice
1-2 that right hand he
whips it down to the body very nicely
very good power
nice body work specifically with that right hand
but his defense
is trying to use his height
in a division
where it's tall ass dudes like he just want to lean back
he want to lean back
and hope that you can't reach his chin
but he leans back with his chin in the earth
hoping you can't reach
Wilder
power
all caps I think y'all all know that
huge big right hand
when he's not trying to book up
and by all the counts he coming into this fight like 220
to 230 or something he's explosive
he's sudden
and
he got one of the biggest hearts in box
now he is willing to he is the
epitome when they say go out on your shield he who you
tone back
when when he when
people say go out on your shield he who you tone back
and the issue
in this fight for Haleini is all the
height that he likes to use
Wilder is taller than him by inch
all the height
that he likes to use Wilder has a four inch
reach advantage
so that lean straight back
is probably going to get his chin punched through
now
Haleini's could possibly hurt Wilder in this fight
but I don't think he going to finish him if he do hurt
and I'm like
Wilder has earned this for me
for the rest of his career
he's just
depend upon who he fight
guys like Haleini
if he ends up fighting somebody like
Andy Ruiz
if I see Wilder getting in fight with Anthony Joshua
those types of guys
pretty much
even if he getting in the ring with
Ussi
anybody not named Tyson Fury
you have to show me that you can take a Wilder
right hand for me to pick you to pick
right now
the only one I'm kind of like
is Joe Joyce
because Joe Joyce seem like
I don't know
I watched him get hit with a club punch
by Joseph Parker I said last night I watched him get hit with a club punch
last time he fought
and his chin didn't move
the dude hit him with a club punch and the dude backed up
so Joe Joyce
maybe he can stand up to the power
Joe Joyce can be Wilder
R-Jack says Ussi too skillful Wilder
but I don't know R-Jack I mean
shit and the Joshua hit Ussi with the right hand
and that's why I'm here
R-Jack like Haleini might be winning the fight
he might be winning the fight like
dudes might be out boxing Wilder
but until somebody either A
shows me that he can go the whole fight without taking his right hand
or B
take his right hand and get up from it
then I got Wilder bro that's what this shit boy down to man
he has earned that shit from me in over 40 fights
knocking out
or putting down everybody he's ever been in the ring with
landing his right hand on literally
everybody he's ever fought
Tyson Fury is more elusive and a better fighter
than Robert Haleini has ever dreamed of being
so if Deontay Wilder can land his right hand
on Tyson Fury
and put his ass down
I know he gonna land his right hand on Haleini
and Haleini's gotta show me he can take it
I don't believe he will I got Wilder by stoppage
and I think it might happen sometime
between the 5th and the 7th round
I think it's gonna be a little bit of ring rush there
I think it's gonna be a little bit
a slow start there
and so you know
I think about between
round 5 and round 7 Wilder get his footing
he'll start really letting that right hand go
and uh we're gonna say good night to
oh Mr. Robert Haleini and that's the other thing
somebody just put it in the chat they sparring
partners bro
these dudes they're sparring together like
Wilder know some
PBC know some
Malik Scott know something
and they didn't spar together like years and years and years ago
Haleini is here Wilder get ready for the
um for the Tyson Fury fight
cause I believe Haleini was on the undercar fighting
Calnaqui
if memory serves me correctly
so yeah bro like I think this is a
setup so I got Wilder
knock out stop
now let's get to Michelle Rivera
oh we gotta go man we gotta keep it going
Michelle Rivera, Jerry Perez
Michelle Rivera is gonna beat Jerry Perez
yeah yeah yeah
I ain't gonna do the whole breakdown for y'all Michelle Rivera 23 and 0
14 knockouts Jerry Perez 14
and 1 11 knockouts the only thing that's
gonna be um kind of
interesting and this fight for me is can
Michelle Rivera beat Jerry Perez
worse than I saw Frank Martin beat him cause Frank Martin
stopped him in like the 6th to 7th round Marquis
what up stopped him in like the 6th to 7th
round but Jerry Perez straight forward straight
back basic defense
and Michelle Rivera got all kind of good lateral movement
nice busy jab
patrols distance well got good power
good punch variations nice left hook
nice straight right hand pull counter right
hand step back counter right hand
fluid with his movements and athletic
and got a good rhythm yeah yeah yeah
Michelle Rivera beat Jerry Perez
I wanna see if he can stop him I hate that this is a
8 round fight though I hate
when prospects like Michelle Rivera go
backwards in the rounds that they fight
he just fought a 10 rounder against Joseph Adorno
now they gotta fight in the 8 rounder
if you got on fighting a guy that they won't
sanction to fight 10 rounds
then have them fight somebody else bruh
this is a clear step back in competition
in my mind maybe it's a stay busy
fight maybe it's a fight just
to fill the card but um
I got Michelle Rivera Mr. aggressive
e-side 512 Nick J. um Dundada
um everybody that's in the building salute
the out hit the like button we about to start the debate in 10 minutes
starting
the debate in 10 minutes
man 10 minutes
we getting it pop
so y'all be ready
alright bumpy what's up with it bumpy
um so
moving on though Michelle Rivera I think
is gonna win that I'm gonna give him unanimous decision
simply off the strength of he only got 8 rounds
if it does get a stopper to be late
about round 5 or round 6
um maybe even round 7 because Michelle Rivera don't
got that one punch put you to sleep
in my opinion he has done it before
but as he's fought tougher guys I don't think he has
has it like that will you most cool what up
so I'm gonna pick him by unanimous decision
wide wide wide wide wide unanimous decision
okay
what they doing um
8 rounds so like 79 72
80 to 71
you know I'm saying some wide ass shit like a snoozer
veto mil nicky junior
versus limberth punts
8 round 154 pound fight
uh plus 754 punts
minus 1600 for mil nicky
as the favorite
mil nicky's 12 and 1 with 8 knockouts
punts is 19
5 with 11 knockouts and he been knocked out one time
mil nicky got every punch
got nice body work
um when he gets it going he got a lot of dog
and the reason I say he got a lot of dog because he lost to a guy named James Martin
and wanted to rematch
and his team signed him up for that rematch
and he wanted that fight he was ready to go for that fight
but James Martin ass couldn't make way
James Martin couldn't make way but
when you got young fighters like that they want to go get that get back
I respect that shit because a lot of young
fighters like that they lose and they just move on
but he lost and he wanted that get back
but James Martin just couldn't make way
um so shout out to him for being willing to do that
um so that's why I say he got dog
very confident and he's growing and every fight I see him getting better and better
um for punts
punts has a wide stand so he has no movement
can't get out of the way of nothing
um he sees a lot in the ring
you can tell he sees what he's supposed to do but he just slower shit
he see that the punch is coming
and he try to get them hands up but he just slow
you know what I'm saying he tough and he'll go some rounds with you
um but I think veto mil nicky gonna walk off
doing bad
I got veto mil nicky winning that fight
um you know relatively comfortable
could get a stoppage but I'm gonna pick him too
by unanimous decision
alright let's get to the ladies man
let's get to the ladies bro
let's get to the ladies
the two in my opinion
these are the fights I'm looking forward to the most
no disrespect to Devin Haney and Camposos
but I feel like that fight is not as competitive
as these fights
and I say that too
combat toolbag what up
no disrespect to Deontay Wilder and Haleinius
you know what I'm saying I'm always down for Deontay Wilder
fight
but these two fights
on Saturday afternoon
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah sign me up
yeah sign me up for these
let's go mccayla mayor or licia bomb gardener first
round super featherweight 130lb
junior lightweight
wbobwbc championship
of the world
mccayla mayor minus 200 for the decision
plus 1200 for the ko minus 300 just to win
bomb gardener
plus 225 to win
plus 500 for the ko
plus 475 for the decision mayor
orthodox fighter 5 foot 9
66 and a half inch reach fighting out of cali
32 years old 17 wins no losses
5 wins by way of knockout
bomb gardener 28 years old orthodox
fighter out of Ohio 5 foot 6
12 wins one lost
7 wins by way of knockout look mccayla
mayor is a high volume fighter
she got every punch that you could think of offensively
she's proven to be tough and durable
because she does get touched up in her fights
she does struggle to cut off the ring
her feet her foot movements to cut off the ring and move laterally
not there her defense in my
opinion is nonexistent
she gets caught with shots in every single fight
but she's able to box through those
she's very good offensively
and so she overwhelms a lot of opponents that she faces
Alicia bomb gardener got good timing
she's an explosive counter puncher
good movement in the ring
good pivots got a good jab
strong step back counter right hand
this fight comes down
to the volume of mccayla mayor
to the timing and the precision of Alicia
bomb gardener if Alicia bomb gardener can time her
precisely with a counter shot
and make her respect her
or even worse for mccayla mayor
hurt her then Alicia bomb gardener will win this fight
if mccayla mayor can overwhelm Alicia bomb gardener
and take her power with no issues
coming forward and she doesn't feel like
Alicia bomb gardener can hurt her
or garner her respect
then mccayla mayor will win this fight
but I think
what people are missing the boat on
because a lot of people are picking mccayla mayor
a lot of people are missing the boat on it
girls don't fight in the rhythm that you see in Alicia bomb gardener
or clipper sashile's fighting
most women boxers don't
they all kind of fight high volume
I'm good offensively
I'm fighting these two many fights so I gotta go in there throw as many punches as I can
and then boom I'm in and I'm out
Alicia bomb gardener is more patient
fights to her timing plays to her athleticism
will move around the ring walk you around the ring
try to walk you in the shots box pivot
she do a lot of shit that a lot of ladies don't do
and so it's hard to prepare for her
and again bro I keep going back
to the most recent fight that I've seen
of mccayla mayor
I watched her not be able to cut off the ring
against Jennifer Hans so why would I believe
she gonna cut off the ring against Alicia bomb gardener
I watched her take right hands
over and over and over again from Jennifer Hans
so why would I believe that Alicia bomb gardener gonna catch her with some right hands
and I think bomb gardener
will make her a respecter so I got bomb gardener
a lot of people say bomb gardener can only win by knockout
I don't believe that
I don't believe that I think that Alicia bomb gardener
fighting in a style
fighting in a rhythm that mccayla mayor
is not used to
she just fought a similar opponent
in Terry Harper who fights the same style
I'ma come forward
I throw a lot of punches
I'm good offensively but I got the same hose mccayla mayor
got defensively I'm straight up
I got t-rex arms
I'm tall but my reach ain't shit
remember mccayla mayor
5'9", 6'6 1.5 inch reach
that means a lot because that means she has to be close to you
to hit you even though she's tall
which means she has to be close to you
because she is all up in the air for you
so I think Alicia bomb gardener will get her respect
I think Alicia bomb gardener's power and her time
and her counter punching ability
will slow down the work rate of mccayla mayor
and I think Alicia bomb gardener
some may call me crazy
is a better boxer from the outside
with her rhythm, her speed, her athleticism
and her foot movement
I think she can outbox mccayla mayor from a distance
and I think that's where the fight is going to be
she's gonna be all reckless and shit
get caught with some hot shit
and she's gonna be like oh shit I gotta slow this shit down
so I got Alicia bomb gardener
I got her by unanimous decision
7 rounds to 3, 6 rounds to 4
but I think she's gonna clearly win this fight
I wouldn't be surprised with a stoppage
but I'm not picking a stoppage in a women's fight
then we got Clarissa Shields
and then everybody that got links y'all can start coming up
I see J chestner in the background
everybody that got the links
put a debate come on up we on our last pick
Marcia 10 round 160 pound
undisputed championship
let me go ahead and drop the link for y'all
smoke right side
kqkc
bftb everybody
y'all come on up man let's get this shit popping
Clarissa Shields Savannah Marcia
Shields minus 120 Savannah minus
110 Savannah's plus
225 for the KO
plus 270 for the decision
Shields plus 850 for the KO
plus 125 for the decision
Shields is 27 years old 5 foot 8
68 inch reach orthodox fighter out of Michigan
12 wins no losses 2 wins by way of knockout
then you got Savannah Marshall
Savannah Marshall is 31 years old
out of the UK orthodox fighter
5 foot 11 and a half
12 wins no losses with 10 wins by way of
knockout
look man Savannah Marshall got big power
and fights at an awkward and unorthodox
ass rhythm she's probably the best
finisher in female boxing right now
once she gets you hurt she's finished everybody
she's gonna be in the ring with so we will give her that credit
Clarissa Shields I mean what can we say
two time olympic gold medalist fast hands
very elusive she can counter punch you
she don't have no power though I know
fans of hers like me you want to see her
get the power we try to say it was the two minute rounds
she's fighting tough competition she don't really
have no power she got enough power
to get your respect
enough power that you'll never walk through her shit
but just not enough to stop you that's all
just not enough to stop you but
she is by far superior
so basically this comes down to
if Savannah Marshall can't hurt Clarissa Shields
she ain't got no shot
if she can't hurt Clarissa Shields
she ain't got no shot whatsoever
bro like she ain't got no shot she can't out box her
so I'm gonna count on Clarissa Shields
not to get hurt I'm gonna count on Clarissa Shields
to out block out box
Savannah Marshall and I think she's gonna win
a unanimous decision against Savannah Marshall
in her own country and that's my picks
for the week hope y'all
enjoy them but I gotta bring my brothers up man
I gotta bring the homies up man
they hurt
they ready they lie
they lit let's go to the moderator
first KQ what's up man
what's up man
hold on chillin man chillin man
let the people know what we can
expect from you as the moderator man how you gonna be hard
monitoring this shit bro man hard
monitoring all damn
hey man look everybody
look when I say hey let's go
let's go soon you start talking
man that's when the time is gonna start
alright now remember everybody got
10 minutes both guys got 10 minutes
in 5 minute we butto
rounds okay keep that in mind
in 5 minute we butto round we are going
3 rounds tonight baby it is lit
it is going on tonight baby
so you might well sit back and relax
and you might learn something alright
so get ready for the
fantastic TKO debate baby
alright wow wow wow
alright go ahead
let's go to do it right
man what can we expect from you bro
man y'all done hurt me judge before
my bad what are you looking for
as a judge man what do we need to do
to impress you tonight
listen I need you to have
good arguments strong points
looking forward to
the butto rounds man
you know what I'm saying energy you gotta have energy
when you end this debate you know what I'm saying
presentation is about
presentation as much as it is anything else
so I'm looking forward to seeing all of that
and I got my notepad ready so
y'all know I will be critiquing every point that you go through
damn near so it is what it is
yes sir yes sir shout out to
St. Louis mix with the 5 dollars in a super chat he say
appreciate the
pics KO speaking of I got
KO by UD don't put no pressure on me
don't put no pressure on me let's go to
smoke smoke man how you judging
tonight what you looking for bro
um yeah
tonight man I'm just looking for
arguments that make sense and persuade me
I'm you know
it's real simple don't contradict yourself
um give me a good
argument um and
yeah you have me
already already and then
let me go to my opponent and my brother
at the same time my brother J chestnut
J chestnut man final
words what you doing man you about
you about to you about to do me bad man what's going on
bro hey man I'm locked in let's get it
bro all right give me a second y'all let me
hit hit be a fuck give me a minute y'all
right everybody doing out there
all right all right
I was gonna say chestnut you taking
um Shakur right
that is correct
all right don't forget
I just got off the phone
if he on his way y'all he be here in a minute
um give me a second
don't forget to head to KQKC
Saturday baby yes sir we are calling
the fights yes sir we gonna be calling
the Deontay wilder fight we gonna be calling
the ladies fight and don't
worry I'm keep you updated on
the Devin Haney fight also
so it is pop and Saturday
all right yeah and we um
and everybody KQKC
right side um
their their links are in the
description and then also BFTB
link is in the description and then
smoke his link is not in the description
because he's the last minute judge he's
stepping in for us on late notice but
please smoke drop your um drop your link
and everybody go subscribe to all these brothers channel
um and so we can get we can
get it popping BF just hit me say
email them the link let me email this to them y'all
and we'll get it popping um while I'm emailing
them to them no just let me explain the rules to everybody
bro um very very simple
we got three rounds
okay we're gonna do a coin flip to see who go first
um and then once we once we do
that um each person have
10 minutes to cook um and then I'm
going to give you the um
give me a second
uh let me get this email sent out
we'll get 10 minutes to cook and then it's a
five minute rebuttal for each one
um BFTB
all right there we go
all right
and then we're gonna go to the judges
we got three judges um
they're all gonna give their reason on
who they thought one and why they picked them
and then we're gonna go on to the next round
it's KQKC said it's gonna be three rounds
we won't talk over each other
we will not um do
anything like that we're gonna let each other cook
we're gonna let each other talk now I just sent the link to
BF he'll be jumping on in a minute um
and let me go ahead and do the coin talks
let me share my screen
real quick
quick
there he is what's up
my bad brother
super apologetic man super apologetic
my bad week
it's all good we you just in time for the coin talks
let me share my screen
and just real quick while I'm sharing my screen let me um
let everybody know
how you judging tonight man what you looking for
what how can we get your vote tonight man
yes sir yes sir so
uh what I'm looking for I'm looking for
um the facts
whatever facts are given
I'm looking for you guys to base your opinions
on those facts
nothing more nothing less
if you can't do that you can't get me
all right
J. Chestnut I'm gonna be your gracious host man
I'm gonna let you call it in the air
what you going with heads and tails
uh heads
uh
all right his head is who you want to go first
take off bro
all right babe let me stop sharing my screen
get the question popping
again this is a tank Davis Shakur steve
it's in debate that's what the questions are based off of
and
I will be arguing for Tate Davis and my brother J
will be arguing for Shakur
steve's in KQ go ahead and read the question
whenever you got your time already and we can get it
All right. All right. The first question is which fighter is in position to be the bigger star in the future?
All right, take off brother
So it's very simple, bro
It's very simple the answer to this question is clearly
unapologetically and emphatically
Javante take days
Reason is in order for you to be in position to be a bigger star in the future
You got to be in position to get the biggest fights that will make you a bigger star
And you got Javante take Dave is who people are begging to fight him
Shakur Stevenson is begging for fights
the two biggest fights of Shakur Stevenson's career Jamel Harry and
Oscar Valdez. I'm old enough to remember that
Jamel Harry
It was in his contract to fight Carl Frampton the WBO said one shall fight y'all got a fight Shakur Stevenson once you win
Jamel Harry beat Carl Frampton and started trying to fight Oscar Valdez. He didn't even want to fight Shakur Stevenson
Luckily the WBO basically made him do it
that was the second biggest fight of
Shakur Stevenson's career the biggest fighter Shakur Stevenson's career
Oscar Valdez
I'm also old enough to remember that Shakur Stevenson had been chasing Oscar Valdez through 126
Then Valdez moved up to 130 Shakur became champion at 130 and what did Oscar Valdez do?
What did Bob Arum do Bob Arum was trying to make Oscar Valdez versus Navarrate now I cannot prove
Why he ended up getting the Oscar Valdez fight?
I would just say that it coincided with the timeline of the moment that Terrence Crawford started suing top ranking Bob Arum
For all that shit he's suing him for the racial shit messing up his career all the shit that we all know about this well documented
The minute that that shit happened then all of a sudden Shakur Stevenson and Oscar Valdez get made
But Shakur Stevenson was complaining about how Bob Arum don't want undisputed unless the person name is Loma and all this other shit
How you don't want to unify unless it's Loma so his two biggest fights he had to beg and plead for meanwhile
Teng Davis his biggest fights Jose Pedroza had no issue fighting him just follow him. He didn't have to beg for that fight
fucking um, um Leo Santa Cruz 4th Division champion
Gary Russell, Jr. Was begging to fight Leo Santa Cruz tank Davis is so set up for success in the future and right now
That he didn't have to do shit Leo Santa Cruz like yeah, I'll fight tank no issue. So
Shakur Stevenson is begging for fights
It's people begging to fight tank Davis last I checked Gary Russell, Jr.
Is calling for a tank Davis fight not a school Stevenson fight
I'm pretty sure you've seen my interviews. You know who I want. I definitely want Javante tank Davis
I still want him never heard Gary Russell, Jr. Former featherweight champion never heard him talk about Shakur Stevenson like that
He did say he did him up in sparring and shit, but he been calling for tank Davis for years now
Hector Louise Garcia just became super WBA champion at 130 pounds
Was he calling for a Shakur Stevenson fight who was also a champion? No, no, no, no, he was calling for tank Davis
I wanted to keep aiming for the top and after beating Colbert and Gucci areas. I want the biggest challenge out there tank Davis
People begging to fight this man. You gotta want people to fight you to be set up to be a star, bro
Michelle Rivera just a prospect just a contender. I've been waiting for a year to become a world champion
It's one of my dreams and the WBA promised me an eliminated bow which hasn't happened
I am the mandatory to Devonte Davis title so he can fight me or vacate the title
Visily Lomachenko he want you want a tank Davis. I don't hear him calling for school Stevenson
Devon Haney his dad said he'll drop belts to fight your volunteer tank Davis
His daddy said he'll move up to 140 to fight your volunteer tank Davis
And it's not just his daddy
It's also the CEO of Devon Haney promotions and his manager
So when he says that they will induce them you kind of got to take him on his word because he manages Devon career
They want to fight tank Davis. I all I hear when Ryan Garcia talk he'll cause Shakur Stevenson a dirty-ass fire fighter
For all them low blows. He'll say that Shakur Stevenson is somebody that's boring
But when it comes to who he want to fight Ryan Garcia, he want to fight tank Davis
Regis pro gray. I ain't never heard him say shit about Shakur. He want to fight tank Davis though
Josh Taylor. I don't hear him talking shit about school. He won't fight tank Davis though
TfE my Lopez. I don't say shit about school. He won't fight tank Davis though
Roller-Romero. I want my rematch with tank Davis. You know, I got five put my ass to sleep six round knock my ass out
I still won't fight tank Davis
Esau people cruise. I won't fight tank Davis rematch. So all of these people at or around
130 135 140 they all want to fight tank. They ain't calling for Shakur
So how is tank not in a better position to be a star in the future if everybody want to fight him?
Now let's keep it moving because there's more reasons bro way more reasons
He will always be attached to the biggest star in boxing history whether he leave Florida not
Tank Davis got people that rock with him simply off the strength of Floyd
He got people that hate him simply off the strength of Floyd
Floor may whether put tank Davis on his Conor McGregor paper view that sold four million dollars tank Davis was a co-main event
She coined never been on the event like that again set up for success in the future
Floyd
Gets a lot of hate and all that shit matriculate down the tank
But guess what what's good about that and what makes him set up for success in the future?
Because people want to see him win and people want to see him lose no disrespect to Shakur
But a lot of people don't care when he fights bro. Everybody in this room do but we're talking about a bigger star in general
Fighting style last I checked tank Davis has a far more exciting fighting style than Shakur Stevenson
Which is what's making him more popular right now? He has a better fighting style the knockouts
The ability to be vulnerable maybe be losing some rounds here at earth
But then put your ass asleep whereas Shakur Stevenson
They say he went a lot of rounds. They say he's boring people were not happy. No one's ever left a tank Davis fight
Upset the way that they left a germine knock a thieler fight when Shakur was fighting him and no one liked their performance
people don't say that shit about tank bro
And then most importantly when you're set up for success in the future. How does shit look right now?
How does it look right now and right now Shakur got some catching up to do tank Davis already got a head start
He's already a bigger star right now. So in order for Shakur to become a bigger star in the future
He got a catch up to his now and pass him right now tank Davis and already did three paper views Shakur got zero
Tank Davis first paper view was when he was 26 years old Shakur Stevenson to be 26 years old in June
He got like five or six months to catch up
So how's he set up for success in the future or to be a bigger star in the future if he's already behind right now?
And then here's the kicker
Shakur Stevenson last fight was in his hometown at the Pudential Center in New Jersey
Tank Davis his last fight was at the Barclays Center in Brooklyn now. I did the Google that 25 miles away from
each other
25 miles away tank Davis winning fault in Shakur's backyard
Shakur fault in his own backyard
Shakur had 10107 people in the building for his Stevenson versus Conceitio fight
Tank Verge roller-mero tank went to his backyard and he had 18,000 people coming to watch him fight at the Barclays Center
Only 25 miles away from the Pudential Center. He's more popular
He set up for success and he's a bigger star in Shakur Stevenson's hometown. This Shakur Stevenson is bruh
Point blank period
And then you got to touch casual fans to be a star right
Last I checked I ain't never seen Madonna at a goddamn Shakur Stevenson fight
Last I checked I ain't never seen little Duval the comedian talk about Shakur Stevenson
I seem to talk about tank Davis before
Last I checked what rap lyric is Shakur Stevenson in because I heard tank Davis name come up in the little baby song
This man got the casual fan base. He set up for success in the future. This man already hot on right now
You said how many minutes two minutes
Okay, this man already hot on right now
So he's already off to a head start
This man is going to be attached to the biggest star in boxing history for the rest of his career
Whether he leave him or not if he stayed with him he the guy on the floor if he leave him
He got a little floor, but he gonna have that floor made with the name regardless of what he do for the rest of his career
He has people from multiple weight classes
Calling to fight him
Which in order for you to be successful
You got to have people that want to fight you to be able to make big fights so you can be a star
He got more people calling his name than Shakur Stevenson in the shit not even close
It's not close bro, so in closing people begging to fight tank
Shakur is begging to fight people
Tank is attached to Floyd Mayweather
Shakur is attached to Bob Averham
Tank is a bigger star right now and has a huge head start
And so he is set up for success
And and and being a star in the future far better than Shakur Stevenson could have a dream of being
Because and I leave it with this closing point
If we go off a recent history
Shakur Stevenson top rank Bob Averham
They might be able to build Shakur Stevenson up to the type of PPV star that Terrence Budd Crawford is
If we go off a recent history, they might be able to build him up to Terrence Budd Crawford
But even Terrence Budd Crawford ain't as popular as goddamn Javante Tank Davis is right now
So even if they build him up if they can make him undisputed
If they can make him a three division champion
If they can do all of that
And he starts fighting on PPV and they can make them and he becomes the number one pound for pound fighter in the world by many
And he becomes just as popular as Terrence Crawford is he still won't be more popular than Javante Tank Davis and I'm done
All right. All right. All right. Let me stop you
Okay
Okay, all right
Okay, you ready Jay?
Let's do it. All right. Okay. Go ahead. Can you hear me? Well, yes, I can yes. I can hit you just well
All right, go ahead. Shoot your shot, baby
All right. That was a cool round. I like that. I like that. Okay, so
The reason why he's not set up for success is honestly
It's too many
It's too many things we don't know about tanks future and what I mean is
Is he with Floyd? Is he not with Floyd before the role in Romero fight?
We remember him saying this my last fight with Floyd. Everybody thought those rumors was true
We thought those was true
Up until this point since the role of Romero fight, we still don't know is he signed with me whether is he not signed with me
Because whether we want to whether my brother knock out one to admit it or not that matters
That matters. He is a big star now
But my question is is it taint? That's the star or is it floyd? That's pushing him to make him the star
That's the real question because the thing that we don't we want to gloss over
What does taint do by itself to make him a star so outside of the ring because to be a star it's more than just
Getting in getting in the ring getting on pay-per-view like like what what what is taint done?
To show that I can be the star of this thing by myself
By myself like I don't need floyd
I don't need Leonard L to be talking from you for the first part of his career when he was on pay-per-view
He wasn't even talking for itself. It was floyd talking. It was Leonard talking hell
Leonard still talking to this day for
For taint. We ain't heard for it, but that's because floyd's still in the shot from so even if he re-signed with floyd
We already seen the type of sucker shit that floyd do to him
Floyd do the shit where I'm gonna announce my exhibition fight
The same time I'm gonna announce your uh the same night you same day you got a press conference for your pay-per-view event
What kind of promoter is that?
To where that guy that guy is supposed to be the one that's supposed to guide you into being the biggest star because your promoter
Has a lot to do which you becoming the star now you do have to do some things yourself, right?
Like you do got to do some things
But when have we heard taint come out and talk that and talk when have we heard taint come out and put that
Smoke on somebody because it's a lot of niggas calling his name. No, you're right. You're absolutely right. It's a bunch
Of people calling his name, but how many names he calling only name wouldn't have seen him go after no doubt about it
Is ryan garcia? Why why ryan?
What ryan got to offer him?
Okay, like so he so he good with fighting with for the money cool. I cool
That's cool
So if you whip floyd
Floyd gonna stunt your growth as a star like like tanks say oh floyd jealous of me
Before jealous of me. Okay. So how is that setting you up to be the big star going forward?
They got you on pay-per-view, but as we seen from buddock ruffin being on pay-per-view is not that's not what makes you a star
We don't see we don't see them on pay-per-view. All right, it's cool. So going forward. There's a difference between
There's a huge difference between
These guys calling for fights calling to fight
To you calling to fight tank davis and tank davis actually wanting to answer that bell
Because guess what knock out if you come to my front door and rain my doorbell, but then I don't answer the door
What do it mean that you came and run the doorbell? It don't mean shit. It don't mean shit because I didn't open up the door
You feel me? So he gonna be he's in position to get the biggest fights, but he has not shown us
That he wants those fights. He is not sad that he wants those fights. What do we do in tanks early career?
We said oh, it was for holding the back for it didn't want them fight
It's for him and when he the first chance he had to clear the air
About that. What did he say? Oh, I didn't even ask for those fights. I ain't even asked to be put in there with no big names
so
We are led to believe that because he's going to be the bigger star because
People are begging to fight him. Yeah, if I was on pay-per-view, you know, I'm gonna get
Good page say yeah, cool. I'll be calling his name too. But what what the hell does that have to do with actually getting in the ring?
See the part you didn't address is how
Are these fights gonna happen because Floyd hasn't shown the shown the willingness to make these fights happen
LRB hasn't shown the ability to make these fights happen tank
Hasn't shown the willingness to make these fights happen. So your guy is the bigger star, but somehow
Somehow
somehow some way
He has not been able to translate his star status into a big fight
So if basing it off of getting the big fights getting the fights that you want that the fans want to see
Chacoor is in the best spot in the best place. Why?
Because on his side of the street side of the street if we're gonna use that
His side of the street all the fighters all the top guys are there. Devon's there. Devon's got all the belts
Lumberchenko's over there. Uh, let me see. T. O.'s over there, but T. O.'s at 140
So, you know, we won't you know leave him off of there, but really the two that I just named
One with all the belts and one that's gonna be fighting next for all the belts
They're all over there. So what tank gonna do because tank can't keep cruising around
Fighting for WBA regular belts
So you so so what we doing? You get what I'm saying? What we doing? So there is a huge difference between
him wanting
People wanting to fight him versus him getting in the ring and fighting anybody
So if he's gonna be the biggest star how we gonna make these fights happen if everybody that I just named involved
Ain't willing to put him in that at least with Bob despite what Chacoor said
Guess what he put him in there when Oscar Valdez. He put him in there with Jamel Herron. He did that
He came out and he called out
Devon Haney Lumberchenko even called out Lumberchenko for some time now
So he's shown the willingness stepping that we any and everybody
But we ain't seen that from your guy
So, yeah, okay. He on pay review now. He can tend with putting anybody
He is content with knocking out whoever they put in the ring with him and they cool with that and honestly on top of all of that
Which Chacoor which Chacoor being on ESPN
Which Chacoor being on ESPN he has the biggest sporting platform in the world behind them and that matters
So I haven't seen any pay-per-view stars since they since top rank went to two ESPN
Can we name a pay-per-view star that came out came out of top rank?
That they that they built no because that's not their business model. They try to put as many eyes on you as
they're trying to put as
Many eyes on you as they possibly can and I'll prove my point
Let's see
Take Davis Leo Santa Cruz. They sold 15,580 tickets with another 200 with another 200,000 pay-per-view buys. That is a total
of
240,000 people let's say if the numbers are accurate 240,000 people you got Davis versus barrios 200,000 people that bought the pay-per-view another
16,570 so that's
2,000 uh
216,000 people that don't watch that fight
People Cruz will give benefit in about 200,000 pay-per-view buys. He had 15,000 people come in attendance
So now you got 215,000 and then the romero fight. I didn't get the box numbers for that one
But he got 275,000 pay-per-views. So that's 270
75,000 people that watched that fight. Okay
Shakur Stevenson without being on pay-per-view his last four fights
Then I could tell you a fight that you said people were so born with
875,000
views average it peaked at 927,000
Jamel Herron
It averaged 1.23
million people watching it at a time val des
1.17 million people watching it average
Uh and his last fight can say see I 1.097 million people watch average
So you can't sit here and say people don't know who he is people ain't watching them because by my math
Every number that I just listed off with him being on ESPN
Not being a pay-per-view fighter
guess what
He got more eyes. So many two minutes Bob
second two minutes
Okay, so with that being said with that being said
He got more eyes on that's that's Bob Aaron's business model
We're gonna put as many eyes on you as we can. That's how he made lomitenko start. That's how he made Tio Fimo start
That's how he made but but Crawford to start. That's just what he do
It's not a pay-per-view model
So he is set up because why because all the belts are on his side right now
In the two the two prominent guys that's standing in his way at 135
Devin Haney
In uh, uh, uh, vasile lomitenko are also on his side of the street. It's a good business bro. I rest my face
All right, you still got a minute and 15. You want to take it? I'm good. Oh, gee. All right. That's the end of that one
All right. Okay. Okay. Oh five minutes five minutes for uh, rebuttal rebuttal
All right
Many of the question was the Shakur want more smoke than tank or
Or this tank really want the big fights or some shit like that then your argument would have made sense
But it made no sense because the question is who is in a better position to be a bigger star in the future
Last I checked you proved my point a couple of times number one
You came out your own mouth and you said tank is the one in position to get big fights
You said that shit you damn self. So you sound like your ass was arguing for me
Then you bought up the views that tank did versus the views that Shakur Stevenson did last I checked
Shakur Stevenson fights was free
So he getting all these views for free
People are paying to watch tank fight bro. Like would you rather have
275,000 people to pay to watch you fight or 1.1 million people to watch your ass fight for free
Would you rather have 215,000 people paying to watch you fight or 1.1 million people
Pay to watch or watch your ass for free or 216,000 people to pay to watch you fight or
875,000 people to watch your ass for free that shit makes no sense as a matter of fact
It proves that tank is the biggest star because more people are willing to pay to watch him fight while they're watching
Your guy that you arguing for for free
And then you said he made bud Crawford a star if Bob Aaron made bud Crawford a star
Why is bud Crawford the B side in negotiation with Earl Spence?
Who's fighting off the same model that tank davis is in?
So if Earl Spence is in a better position then Terrence Crawford using your logic
And he has the same exact manager that tank davis has doesn't that mean that tank davis is in a better position
For future success since he's working off the Earl Spence model and Shakur Stevenson is working off of the bud Crawford model
And we see how that shit worked out for bud
Just just something to consider bro
Floyd announced an exhibition
On the same day as tank davis
He announced an exhibition on the same day as tank davis his press conference
And then tank davis went out and sold more paper views than he ever sold in his entire paper view career
So how is floyd the one that makes him the star and if you announce your shit on the same day that i got a press conference
Don't that mean you trying to hurt me?
So what do you mean is it floyd is a tank is it floyd is a tank? It's clearly tank bro
It's clearly tank bro
Floyd tried to sabotage this man and he went out and sold more than he had ever sold
Then you said
Is he with floyd or not?
People need to know that because that matters as to who is in the better position
Well all the fighters i named them are opening around they don't seem to give a fuck
They don't seem to give it a goddamn michelle reverberate don't care who he went
Devin haney don't care who he went
Macilli Lomitinko don't care who he went
Regis pro grade don't care who he went Ryan Garcia don't give a damn if this floyd or alhaman or any of them
They don't care who he went
No one cares who tank davis is with except you everybody's still calling their phone
Everybody's still trying to make that goddamn fight
So i don't understand
What you talking about bruh and then let me see if i can rebuttal some more stuff
But you really didn't say much of nothing um oh um
Yeah, i mean shit
I rest my case bro i rebutted that i rebutted that i rebutted that that's gone. That's dead
That's dead. Oh she cool side of the street
The side of the street shit the people that you name and he on the side of the street with devin and loma
They ain't even called him as a matter of fact devin
Responded to she cool stevens his call out by going in on keeshawn davis
That's how little people is is even considering she cool right now devin haney's response to she cool stevens his call out
was to little boy
keeshawn davis
He ain't say shit about she cool
But he's still talking about tank during fight week
He's talking about tank davis right now during fight week bro
What what are we talking about loma chinko loma chinko talking about devin?
I ain't hear him say shit about i ain't hear him say shit about uh about she cool. He said he want to go for undisputed
So so again bro tank davis is set up a way better success in the future
I think I rebutted everything quite well appreciate you man, but uh, hopefully you can you know bounce back a little harder man
But that's all I got for round one
All right. All right. All right jay go ahead and do your thing. You got five minutes, baby
All right, that was that was cute that was cute. So
Let me see what you say you say everybody knocking on the door for tank davis
For tank davis everybody knocking on and again again. I say there is a difference between
people calling for fights
And you actually fighting because to become the bigger star to to to be in that position
You have to have shown the willingness to fight the best
Tank davis has not done that his team has not done that so whether it's florid talking linda talking tank not talking
They haven't shown the willingness
to get in there and fight nobody so
People calling him out. What does that matter because they ain't showed the willingness to fight nobody. Okay, cool
You said Shakur begging for fights. Okay, so
Let's want somebody to fight the best the same thing that fighters get
criticized for oh you didn't call his name out
Shakur I hear calling people name out, but that's begging for fights. Okay, cool. All right, whatever
Devin and already caught out of my you write about that. Guess what? No willing they've shown no willingness to fight him
Right. So so so this position is based off of what other people are doing and not what tank davis is doing
So you're basing it off of oh everybody calling his name everybody calling his name. So he's gonna become the biggest star
why because
He don't fight these dudes and these dudes keep they name keep his name in their mouth like I I don't I don't get it
I don't get it. I don't get it. You use the arrow in your right hand
You use the arrow. You use the arrow Spence
Would you say arrow Spence was on the same model when he's a bigger star than Crawford who's also with with top rain?
Yeah, but the part you forgot is
What made Earl a bigger star? It doesn't mean that Crawford's not a star. What made Earl a bigger star
Then Crawford is who he fought who the fuck is taint fall you give him saying he just on paper if you vote
Knockout sell we know that in boxing knockout sell, but what is he outside of that?
What happens when those knockouts stop?
Is he still the biggest star?
We don't know that we don't know that when Floyd stopped feeding these b and c level fighters that he can knock out
Is he still the same star because that's that's what the real question is see knockout them put all this illusion on y'all like
Uh, this person calling this this person calling this. Yeah. Yeah, they calling his ass up
Yeah, because he ain't he he he eating food right now. He knocking out food. That's in the rain
They feeding them food. He knocking them out. You know what I'm saying? I get it knock out sell it look good
You get the casuals you look good, but they don't know like we know so cool. All right cool. Let me see you said
You said Brooklyn is I believe I don't want to miss quote you so my bad if I do
Uh, you said let me see varkley's new jersey less than 20 miles. He put 15,000 with uh, he put
15,000 with roley in the building less than 20 miles from where she cool father shako only did 10,000
Okay, cool, but the part you forgot is that Baltimore is less than 200 miles away from Brooklyn?
So so so they had shit to do with it, huh?
They had nothing to do with it. Okay, cool. All right, you know, whatever. Um, let me see
Did I did I catch everything? And then the thing is tank is just content with not fighting the best dog
That's just what it is bro. So in position
Is he really in position because all he's gonna do is fight who they put in front of him that he ain't calling for
None of these best fights. That is what it is, bro. I
Yeah, bro, I rest my rebounder, bro. All right, you got a minute 20 left. All right. I'll do it. Oh gee. All right. Okay
All right. That's the end of the first round, baby. All right. Let's let's vote
But first of all, we're gonna first go to dub right side. How you feel, dub
Man, it was a interesting round very entertaining. Um, from what I got
to my first page man, so
K. O. Man, he started off strong. He started off strong and one of the things that stood out in the round to me when he brought up
People begging to fight tank and Shakur begging for fights. That that was I thought that was a very
Elegant way of putting that spoke on how herring and valdez
They really didn't want to fight and the only reason the valdez fight happened was because uh, bud's lawsuit against bob
And he felt that bob. That's why you put him in the ring
Um, then he also he went down and he began naming
Uh, the fighters that are begging for fights with tank, you know what I'm saying? Um
The other thing he brought up was the attachment to floyd may whether we all know how great
Or the superstar or that floyd brings to the sport. So him being attached to floyd's name
Regardless, it'll always be there and that's going to help
Or propel tank now he brought up how uh, k. O. Sell and how tank has the the potential to lose rounds
Which will also bring people to the sport or have people wanting to watch that fight
Even though they that nine times out of ten it seemed like tank don't end up getting to stop it. Um
Let me see he also he brought up how at 26 years old that was
Tanks first pay-per-view and he has three three pay-per-views now where Shakur
He'll be turning 26 in june and it doesn't seem like he's gonna have a pay-per-view
before then so how
Because of that Shakur is already behind the eight ball. Um, he also brought up how tank brought out about 8 000 more people
in Shakur's backyard the star power
That tank brings also brings the casual fan base
Uh, and once again, he kind of ended this round and I like I said a very strong point in my opinion
Uh, how people are begging to fight tank and Shakur is begging for people to fight people
You know what I'm saying and so uh, uh, also he brought up how
um
How but or buzz status as far as what bob did form over at espn
And how even right now tank is a bigger star than bud is as far as pay-per-views go that type of thing and
More or less correlating Shakur's career with uh, buzz career because they were both under top rank
Then chestnut, uh, j. He came out man the first thing he said or the first thing he brought up what he knows about tank
You know what I'm saying saying that uh, uh, if tank if he does or why is it?
Why isn't he taking the biggest fights right?
Um, why he turning down those fights and how can you become a star when you turn fights like that down?
Um, also is he really with mayweathered right or not? He brought up how um
Tank led allowing Leonard to talk for him. You know what I'm saying how tank isn't out there really selling himself
Uh, he brought up the question does floyd stunts does he stunt tanks growth?
Excuse me, and then he really home being on tank not fighting the biggest fights even though people are calling for him
um
And he also brought up how Shakur has uh, the bigger fighters on his side of the street speaking of devin and loma tanko
Uh, and those fights being more opportune or having a better opportunity to be made
Um, man, he brought up then he went into the numbers on Shakur at espn brought up how tank
the the different, you know numbers on pay-per-view that he sold
Versus the how so many more people tuned in to Shakur
on espn
So in the rebuttal round man, we had k.o. He came out and I will tell you the rebuttal round is what did it for me
k.o came out and started dismantling points. Um
He came or you know saying that regardless if tank if he's taking the fights or not
Everybody's still calling his name and whether he's with ford may whether or if he isn't it seemed like and he said you jayson
So he said it seemed like you the only person who cares even though I agree with you
in that
on that part
but um
He also said how even though Shakur did have more eyes on them
Those were all free, you know, it was free views that he was getting there
um, he brought out how bud was the b side over even though he was uh promoted by top rank now that he's moving over
to show time to fight ejay. He's the b side and um
Tank is following down to the same or taking the same route that ejay took as far as becoming a star
um
and also how uh
If one of how devin didn't respond to Shakur, he he suned. I believe that's what k.o says sun kishan in passing
Jay and your rebuttal man, you came out and you brought up how uh once again ejay the reason he's a bigger star than bud is because he fought
The better fighters. I thought that was a really good point. Um, then you also brought up how
k.o's sale, but
We don't know how much they'll sell afterward when tank really gets in the ring or not how much they'll sell
But we don't know if tank will be k.o. Anyone if he's not uh getting fed food
You brought up how everybody they put in the ring with tank is sub par competition. Um, you rebuttal k.o's point about
Uh, 8 000 in brooklyn in shakur's backyard by saying hell balsamore is close to me
I think you said it's about 200 miles away. I don't know. Hey, hey, it sounded good. So, um, and then you also brought up how
At the end of the day man tank. He ain't he ain't calling for the best man
He he's team trying to fight the best. I thought that um
Overall man, I gave the round to knock out the reason I gave it to him is because uh, I think the points that he rebuttled
um
I had to go and neck and neck and to the rebuttal round and I think he did a better job of rebuttling some of your points
And so I gave the round a knockout
All right. All right. Oh that smoke. What's up smoke? What you got, baby?
What's up peace everybody, um, man, that was a hell of an opener. Um
Uh
I got fan friendly style with celebrities and casuals
versus
eyes size of the street and competition
So fucking that's a hell of a thing to have to put pick between
um
man, uh
You know, um
I'm gonna go with uh, I'm gonna go with knockout
by by the slimmest margins and it's really about
Uh, just the meat on the bone
Um
Yeah, just because yeah Shakur can't have all the guys
He can have all that people that if he doesn't put butts in seats that doesn't matter not everybody on top rank
is a star
Uh, unfortunately, um
Yeah, uh, yeah that fat. Yeah
Uh, but then it again it is it is about the future not right now
I understand that
but, um
Yeah, all things given being equal. I like to rebuttal a lot
I um, you you pulled it out of the fire like yeah like mentioning that basically tanks a hometown fighter too
um
Yeah, man. That was that that was very there's a very close and I like your side of the street. I love I love your esp in argument
If you could just if you would have just like kind of tied that into how the Shakur is going to capitalize off that
um
Yeah, then I yeah, uh, yeah, that's that's knocked out by the slimmest and martyrs the head of the chitty chin chin
All right. All right. What's going on grave digger bf tb. What you got, baby? Hey, um, listen man
I respect everybody. I have no beef with nobody but so I'm a blunt dude. I've always been blunt
I will always be blunt. I don't know. I I am judging for myself. I'm not speaking for dubs
I'm not speaking for get this vote. That was in very very clear and easy round for kale
All right. I got no just no just no shade for nobody
I'm my brother the question was who is in position to be the bigger star
now now
I I as a judge I feel like if I if I try to sugarcoat it or if I try to
Beat around a bush. I'm not helping anybody. The question was who is in a position to be a bigger star
my brother j chestnut spent
his entire time talking about how tank is tied to floor
He said one thing that I that I fuck we're heavy when he said the size of the street and who Shakur is fighting
That meant something to me because that is the potential to who can be the bigger star because he's actually fighting somebody
But you spent your entire time when kao said
Tank is tied to fluid
The biggest guy in the sport of boxing you you spent your entire time talking about how tank is tied to fluid
Then tired. I'm see it. I'm like I'm waiting for them. Okay, Jay
Go somewhere else when we go. This is you're improving my man's point and and and
People are gonna. Yeah, I know all the BFT by but I don't give a fuck about none of that
Listen, bro. The question was who was in position to be the biggest star. It was not close
All right, I don't know what my brother's is talking about but it's just slimming some margins
No, it was not it was if the slimmings of margins is uh, Chris rock racing huesane bolt
Then that's what this limit some margins. It was all right. This was a talk road. This is no disrespect to nobody, bro
But I'm keeping it a buck where I'm not gonna lie. I'm not lying nobody bro
I'm not this ain't we don't get participation trophies in this. This was a one-sided landslide. All right, kao won this
badly
But that size of the street part
I definitely fuck with that because you know who Shakur fighting is what's going to make him the bigger star
But the fact that all the people you're talking about who should work and fight one of my tank
These guys ain't called the quarter coliff tank that right there just made it
It was a very it was uphill battle. You really did cover that size of the street should I
Wish you would have stayed there and folks on who he's fighting on that
I wish you would have stayed there because that that right there would have brought you back
But for me, that was a landslide kale
All right, there you go. All right. Okay, everybody get your votes in
I need for everybody to vote in the chat
Everybody all right
Okay, so right now
That was the first round went to ko knock out boston a6 tv. So let's get the chat. See what you got
They voted we closed the vote and they um they they had they had
They had they had me they had me over jay. We I keep the voting going while the judges are voting
Then when the judge get done, we we take it down, but we we move on around to I got the question
I can't see it on here. Okay. All right. All right. Here we go round number two, baby. Yes, sir. All right, wish fighters
Legacy will move would be more talked about when they finish
All right, this is 10 minutes on ko, baby
I hope not it's on jay. It's on jay. Okay. You want first one? Okay jay. Go ahead jay. It's 10 minutes on you. Yes, sir
I already one week the question again
I'm already
All right. No, no, no, you good. All right. Okay
Which fighters legacy will be talked about more?
Okay, so there is a little bit of project been going on here, but
If both of these fighters were to stop fighting today
Stop fighting right now today
What would we remember them for?
Because legacy is something that is it can be subjective, but it is based on what you've done, right? It is based on the
The illusion that's left. What did you leave on the sport of boxing?
What what what did you leave on the sport of boxing?
What did you leave on the sport of boxing?
The thing I can't get away from is we've asked
Time and time and time again from tank davis
To fight somebody fight an elite level fighter
You are supposedly a quote-unquote three division world champion
But you've yet to step in the ring with an a level opposition yet
Your legacy matters because the fights that you win the fights that you not even the fights that you win the fights that you take
They matter. That's what your legacy is about in boxing when lose a draw
You got in the ring with somebody why do we respect Wilder because Wilder took the chance and fought
Uh Tyson fear three times three times. Why do we respect someone like Earl Spence? His legacy if he stopped fighting today
He fought most of the top guys at the time
On his resume
And when we look at tank davis when we when we really scope and look at his four best wins
Jose Pedroza
Which he was undefeated at the time so that's a good win
Leo Santa Cruz
a smaller fighter
That he met at 135 cool or 130. I'm sorry
Mario Barrios who none of us thought anything high of and it took him 12 rounds
His fourth best win it took him 12 rounds
Um
To knock out gambola and those are his title fights. Those are his four title fights
So not for best wins before his four title fights or whatnot
So he fought gambola for a 135 wba regular. He fought barrios for 140
Uh wba regular which my man knockout nusset out his own mouth. He don't count those as regular world championships
So going by his own logic. We only got
Two real belts that that tank is one he won one against leo santa Cruz. He wanted the super wba at 130
and he won the ibf 130 from Pedroza
so
When you look at my guy when you look at my guy
He beat he gave um
Oscar Valdes his first loss 130 pound unification which that is something that tank davis has never done
He's never unified
In any division he's been he's been in three three divisions. I mind you so
Jamel heron coming up the best win of jamel heron's career after he was going no after he went over to pond and knocked out car frampton
And the winners first world title he beat undefeated joey gunzales
right
so
I'm gonna just put this in perspective for you guys, right?
tank davis
Tank davis so right now if we were to end their careers
We would say that chicor has accomplished more right?
His legacy will be remembered more and to to intensify that point
We would I could would tell you that tank davis. Did y'all know that tank davis has been a champion
He won his first world champion before my guy was even a professional fighter
Before my guy was a professional fighter
Tank davis was a champion. So how is it that your legacy will be remembered more?
When you've had a longer reign as a champion that my guy has had in his career
And you still haven't fought the opposition that my guy has fought
And I didn't even bring up the knocker till you fight. I didn't even bring that and we saw what knocker till you know
I'm turned into we're not seeing that right okay cool
So now when we look at it in in my brother knockout his debate when he did um
Bam Bam Rodriguez versus uh monster anyway, what did he tell us? He told us it's competition
over accolades
it's competition
Over accolades so is anybody in here going to argue that tank davis has fought the better
competition
Than Shakur Stevenson
In less fights in less time as a pro
Are we going to argue that?
So my question is how is his legacy going to be remembered?
more than Shakur's
When tank doesn't have a legacy win on his resume
We're still waiting on the legacy fight for tank, but we are going to argue
That tank's legacy is going to be remembered more than Shakur's when Shakur's been a unified champion
When Shakur's fought the better competition
I don't know man sound crazy. I rest my case
Okay, you got about four minutes left. No, I'm good. All right
Okay, it's your turn. You got 10 minutes. Okay. Go ahead and shoot it
I know it's hard for you to believe but I want easy on you in the first round
I'm going to turn up in the second round because I'm gonna rebut your shit then do my rounds
You have nowhere to go and for anyone in the chat. I think somebody say that the shit was fixed
You don't understand my brother j. Chesna was the one who picked these first two questions
So don't say my shit is fixed. I just debate what we debate and so you said you first of all you try to
First of all you tried to change the question you said if both fighters stopped today
What would they be remembered for but that ain't the question the question is which fighters legacy would be more talked about when they finish
Then you bought up tanks wins you started talking about tank again
More than you was talking about the core. Jose Petraza barrios. Leo Santa Cruz gambler
That ain't got shit to do with who will be remembered more when they finish
Then you talked about tank davis accolades and how he ain't got shit and I did say that regular felt don't mean shit to me
And then you tried to quote me, but you didn't tell the people what the question was
Yes, when I was arguing for bam, right reggae is over anyway. I said who you fight matters
But the question was not which fighters legacy will be more talked about when they finish
The question in that particular round was who has the better resume two completely different questions
But hey man, it is what it is you talked about Shakur being unified champion and how Shakur
Basically has better accolades and tank davis. So people are going to talk about him more
When he finishes now
I find that hard to believe because he has more accolades right now today
But people still talk about tank davis right now more than they talk about Shakur Stevenson
Like off the rip he gets more talked about now more people watch him fight now
More people care about what he got going on right now
He is capturing the eyes and the imagination of the general public in a way that Shakur Stevenson can only dream about catching them
So somehow if they both stop fighting right now, all of a sudden people are going to talk about Shakur more
They're going to talk about them more when they ain't talking about them more right now while they're fighting
And they don't have no more or they don't have no more shit to build
So let me get this straight Shakur is a two two division champion. He's unified right now
People are talking about tank way more than him right now
Way more than him, but somehow they stopped fighting today
People are going to talk about Shakur more because of his accolades
But they ain't talking about him more right now because of his accolade
He ain't even talking about more right now while he fighting bro
Anyway, I'll continue so
Tank davis will be remembered more and people will talk about his career more than Shakur Stevenson's when it's over
And when they finish they will talk about him more because the excitement that he brings to the sport
They will talk about him more because your legacy in order for people to talk about your legacy more
That means more people have to care about you
That means more people have to care what you had going on
And he has already showed that more people care about what he has going on than what Shakur Stevenson has going on
Furthermore boxing history tells us that the more exciting more popular fighter
Accolades be damned is the one that people talk about well, uh knockout. What do you mean by that?
Let's talk about some more facts. Shall we?
Bernard Hopkins and Roy Jones Jr.
More people talk about Roy Jones Jr.
And how great he was how he was pound for pound and in his prime
He was overflowing as the pound for pound fighter and they talk about him way more than they talk about
Bernard Hopkins the only time somebody mentions
Bernard Hopkins anymore is when they're talking about some stupid shit that he didn't say about a golden boy fighter
Or about Canelo Averrez, but would you know Bernard Hopkins was undisputed Roy Jones Jr. was not
Bernard Hopkins was the oldest champion in boxing history at 46 years old
Roy Jones Jr. was not
Bernard Hopkins beat Glenn Johnson
Felix Trinidad in his prime in 2001
While Roy Jones beat him in 2008
He beat Oscar de la Jolla
He beat Antonio Tarver the dude that beat Roy Jones Jr twice
He beat Winky Wright and he beat Kelly Pavley. He has a much better much more decorated resume than Roy Jones Jr
But people talk about Roy Jones Jr. more to this day because he had a more exciting
And he had a funner fight style
Evander Holyfield Linux Luit
People talk about the real deal Evander Holyfield to this day
More than Linux Luit because of the fights that he put on because he was more exciting than Linux Luit
Linux Luit was a better fighter
Beat everyone he ever been in the ring with even a vengeance only loss
But they talk about the real deal more because he caught the imagination in the eyes of the general public
Mike Tyson Linux Luit got damn. I'm on fire. Linux Luit beat Mike Tyson ass
Who they talking about more to this day?
Who they talking about?
They talking about Mike right Mike got podcast and shit. You have to remind
You have to remind people how cold Linux Luit was
You have to remind them
Floyd Mayweather, Manny Pacquiao
Manny Pacquiao is the eight division champion and Floyd is like a four or five division champ
Manny Pacquiao got far more accolades than
Floyd Mayweather
Two times the division
But people talk about Floyd to this day because Floyd caught the imagination
of the general public
so tank davis
In the same vein as Mike Tyson in the same vein as Evander Holyfield in the same vein as Roy Jones jr
Tank Davis has already proven because I got voted for a 3-0 in the first round
He is proving without a shadow of the doubt that more people care about him right now
More people care about what he got going on right now
So how's this and they don't give a damn she course. They was in man. You two division champion. They don't give a damn
She course. They was in your ass them became unified champion at 130. They don't give a damn
They don't give a damn bro. You know what they say
Man, what's David's gonna do next? You know how she cool gotta come up. He gotta miss weight
She cool gotta miss weight and then people start talking about
Tank Davis all he gotta do is just exist
All you gotta do is exist in about five minutes
Devon Haney will have a tweet form Ryan Garcia will have a tweet form every interviewer
Ask every fighter in and around his weight class about your Vonte tank day
About your Vonte tank day
So
In order for you to be which fighters legacy will be more talked about when they finish
The person that will be the more talked about is always and I have proven
It will always be the person who catches the attention
Of the general public. It will always be the person who has more people caring about him
When they fight more people cared about mike tyson and he was more popular than linux when they fought
He's more popular post career more people cared about robert jones junior than bennard hopkins
While they were fighting
So guess what robert jones happens to be more popular post career people talk about him more post career
Floyd may whether many packy our same thing. Evander holyfield linux louis same thing
So
I don't know what we talking about bro. I really don't know what we talking about, bro
If the question again was who has the better resume like you tried to bring up the inner way and bam
Rod reggae's debate if the question was who has the better resume than that would have been a good point that you made
But I ain't the question the question is very simple
Who's gonna get talked about more and the answer is very simple
The guy who's being talked about more right now is gonna be talked about more when they get done
Shout out to lord re with that 20 dollars in the super chat tank beats everybody. I rest my cake. All right
There you go. Okay jc. You got five minutes on the rebuttal baby. All right. You ready?
Already
All right. All right. Go ahead shoot your shot, baby. So you made that whole round about you made that whole round about
Fighters who have won fighting and still the thing you forgot to say the thing you forgot to say
What's also tied into the legacy is the fights that we remembered them for a fighting. So yes exciting styles. Okay, cool
Yes, we get that
But also with every one of those fighters that you name we can name two to three
Fights that they are synonymous with whether they won that fight or whether they lost that fight
so what you're telling me is that
looking
projecting forward
We're saying that tank can continue to knock out tomato cans
and because his style is framer friendly
We're gonna go against the whole history of boxing whole history of boxing of
Fighters exciting fighters being tied to top competition win or loss because I said that in my opening round
Not opening round but but my round that it doesn't matter that you win or lose the fight
It matters who you get in the ring with so all those guys that you name and you name by iconic fights
So I don't have to go over that again, but guess what they got in the ring
So those fights are synonymous with their legacies because that's what matters in boxing. What did you do?
Yes, your style matters and we've seen Shakur
Pick up his style. You said nobody cares. Nobody you said more people watch tank
But I just gave you the espn number so uh, uh, I'm gonna go back and I'm gonna read them again. So clearly
875,000 people if that was the average for the for the knockout till you fight clearly 875,000 people cared about that
1.23 million against Jamel Heron
Oh, uh, uh 1.17 million against Oscar Valdez 1.097 million so free or not
Clearly clearly those numbers matter clearly all those people mattered
They they they thought Shakur mattered clearly, right?
I'm just saying so so when we talk about excitement. Yes excitement does matter
KO's do sell but when your legacy is wrapped up and tied up
It matters at the end of the day who you got in the ring with and when we look at tanks legacy
Who are we going to be able to look back and say?
Oh, he got in the ring with this dude. Oh, he got in the ring with this dude. When lose a draw?
We don't have that. So what is he gonna be talking about for it? Oh, he's gonna be talking about oh, he was cool
Oh, he was cool. You know you pay for you starting now. He knocked out some folks
But we never got him we never saw him versus death
We never saw him versus Shakur. We never saw him versus Loma now. I'm projecting. So I don't want that
That's not fact. I'm projecting that but that's what that's
What we're remembering. So all those fighters you name cool. Good job naming them
But they also have fights and resumes and fighters that we can look at that they got in the ring with
And that's that's a part of their legacy too. So it's not about the win-loss. It's not about just the exciting style
You have to mix that sir
With who they got in the ring with and tank. Davis does not have that as of this moment. I rest my case
All right. Okay. Well, you got five minutes
Kio
You ready go ahead
Yes, sir. Oh, so you got to mix the style with who they fought and who they've been in the ring with and big fights matter
Anybody got a moment for Shakur Stevenson is better than the moment that tank Davis had against the four division champion and Leo Santa Cruz
Knock out of the year has Shakur Stevenson had a moment even close to that since we talking about moments and fights and what fights
They'll be remembered for what we remember in Shakur for
Is it the Jamel Heron performance the Jamel Heron and had already lost twice
And had to move up and down and wait the same Jamel Heron that we just saw get not got get his ass beat up by a prospect
So when you talk about they got to have exciting
Styles and moments let's say that let's say I give you that tank ain't got no moments
What moment Shakur had and then let's say I give you the exciting point where we know that tank is more exciting than Shakur
So he'll still be more talked about simply off the strength of being more exciting because Shakur is not excited like tank is
So if the fights that you fight matter, I'm trying to I'm trying to see like is there a four division champion that we can point to
That Shakur Stevenson has fought
Has Shakur Stevenson fought at three weight classes yet?
Has Shakur Stevenson ever got knocked out of the year
I think we all know the answer to those questions
Every last one of them are in favor of Javante tank Davis and my opponent keeps talking about tank far more than he talks about Shakur
He ain't bringing up Shakur's moments because he ain't got none
He ain't bringing up his opponents. He keeps he keeps shitting on he keeps shitting on barrios, right?
I heard him shit on leo a little bit. I heard him shit on jose pedrasa a little bit
But I mean what we what we talking about we talking about iskav out there
The same iskav out there is that a lot of people feel like lobster can say see how the same cheap nass iskav out there
Right or we talking about knock a thiever. We talking about jamael here and like do we really?
Seriously think that anybody that tank date that Shakur Stevenson has fought can hold the count on the tank date
So to get back to the question just to wrap it all up
Which fighters legacy will be talked about more when they finish?
It has to be the guy that's talked about more now now he keeps saying people cared about Shakur steams
And that's why he had all the free views so we not gonna act like some of his fights didn't come on the tail end
of a football game
See when tank davis fight on paper view
He that's it ain't no program and leading into his shit other than his card that he got to carry all himself
And people buy that shit
Shakur steams and in his views and shit that's cool
That's good, but we gonna act like somebody wasn't it with a college football game in front of him
We we gonna act like that didn't happen
Like like we we gonna act like he just got all them views because people was caring about him
Or did they just step away from the tv when the back football game was off and go do something else
But they left the tv on i don't know i'm just saying
I'm just saying bro
So again the more exciting fighter the one who has had the better more i agree with j chestnut
The person with the better moments in the most exciting fight in the fights that people remember
Those are the ones that people are gonna remember you for and they'll be talked about more. Well the roly remiro moment
They talk about what tank davis did to roly way way more than they talk about what Shakur did to ask about theirs
Or what Shakur did to jamele they talk about what tank davis again did to leo santa cruz or jose pedraza
They talk about that shit to this day more than they talk about anything Shakur stevens and has ever done
He got the excitement he got better moments
And he's just gonna be talked about more in the future because he's talked about more right now and it's that simple
I'm not gonna keep beating the dead horse. That's my second round
All right
All right. Yes, sir. That's two rounds down
One ago. We are in the championship rounds. All right. We got my man smoke. What kind of smoke you got smoke
All right, um, so for me I got the triple on tondra, uh knockout
by knockout
Because a knockout of the year
There it is. That was the winning argument. Yeah, uh, that's easy
All right
That's all you have on it
Yeah, you know, I just I just do the winning arguments. Yeah knock out the year one it
All right. Okay. B. L. T. B. Best fight the best. What's going on there? What you got?
um
I'm not going to resay what I said the first listen bro
The question was which fighters legacy will be more talked about more when they finish. That was the question
Um, and my brother j. Chesna. I respect you to death king, but you spent all your time talking about tank davis
So I was waiting for you to um talk to
This is what I would have did because I listen bro. This was an easy k around this what I would have did in this in this
I would have talked about
The fights that could happen because you can't you you the point that you made about where they're at where the fighters are at
Very valid. They're with top rank very valid, right? So what I would have did is I would have talked about
What would have happened? I mean the fact that it's a it it those guys want to fight tank
But it's an easier to fight Shakur. So how would those outcomes have looked?
I would have talked about how Shakur would beat them how Shakur would beat loma chenco
How Shakur would beat the guys who were calling for tank?
I would have talked about that because that's more in line with the question
Answering the question of which fighters legacy will be talked about more, right? Because if if we're talking about
It went when you when you said if he stopped today
That's sort of that changed the whole legacy of the nothing legacy
But it changed the whole dynamic of the question if they stopped today, right?
Because if they stopped today, then I see knock out a year hell is in my intro
Knock out of the year that he knocked out Leo's and accrues in devastating fashion
And all they talk about is tank being one of the most destructive punters and all the boxing
I don't know what Shakur is now. I'm just giving it a buck. There's no shade or hate hate hate
No, no, no, I didn't do that, but when people say when people talk about when they say Shakur, they say what?
He's a boxer. He's probably one of the best boxers or or
But when they say tank, they say one of the most destructive punters in the sport of boxing
That's what they say. So it's like if they stopped it, you killed yourself with that. Don't brother
You killed yourself with that King with that right there bro because now I'm looking at okay
I got to go with my brother said stop today. They stopped today. I see Leo
I'm looking at knock a tiny tukituki and
Leo if they stop today is tank all day if they stop today
yeah
I'm fucking with you king, but I
Is you you pushing away from the question my brother?
Easy KO round again easy KO round and I think you did that to yourself because you you give him you give him his points
Like I'll focus on Shakur god focus on Shakur and run that if you give him his points
It's kind of hard to separate between what he's
They're doing and what you're doing
Just just constructive criticism king, but easy KO round
All right. All right. Very very good. Very good. But uh
Um, um talk all right. We got dub right side coming in and they rear
Right side
My bet I had my I was double muted my apologies
I ain't I ain't gonna hold you on this and I normally I would go through all the points
Not no need to in this situation gate around the KO man. I'm gonna tell you j
I'm gonna tell you j you can't get do not give the opponent credit do not give that man credit for anything that he's saying
Don't don't see and
Man, I'm literally over here. Yeah, and I'm like man. That's why I double muted myself because I'm like when you have four minutes left
I'm like use your time use your time. It was just certain things going on in the round
I felt like you were you were headed in the right direction
And then it just kind of you you kind of you cut you you chopped yourself off at the knees at certain points
You know what I'm saying?
Don't give KO any credit when you're debating the brother. He don't need your help. You feel me?
He don't need it. And so I just I wish you would uh, uh, stuck to Shakur a little more broke down. Um
What what he could do, you know, I'm saying to build that legacy up when you said we cut it off right here
Hell Shakur 25 and tank damn near 28
So tank like you said, what tanked a bit of champion longer than Shakur has been in the fight or been professional
So you can't don't cut it off
You know what I'm saying man? I just wish you would have went more into Shakur
And what he can do to build his legacy. You feel me? So I gave ground to KO man
Like I say, do not get that man. No help man. Do not give him help in your next round brother
All right
Okay, we heading to the championship rounds. We got the next question. All right
Yeah, give me a second. Give me a second. Okay
All right, don't forget Chris the shield's fighting
Saturday morning, Saturday afternoon one o'clock since the time
Come on. Let's support the women fighters. All right. Okay. Let's go. All right the last question
All right the last final championship round we got who wins and why
If the fight
does happen
Now, all right, it's saying Dave. It's saying Dave. You oh you got the time already in my bed
I'm just ready to take off. You got the time already. Oh, all right. Okay. Yes. Go ahead, kill. All right. I got
All right
Tank Davis obviously
And it's for a few reasons. Number one
He's the second most accurate puncher in boxing. That's a fact can't be disputed
But just his his overall counter punching ability he can box with anybody. He's the more explosive fighter
His ring got cute to set people up and stop them
Whether it's faking down low with a faint down low and then coming over the top with a right hook against mario barrios
walking rolly-rimiro into a mean left hand or seeing it that that leo santa cruz was throwing the same
Combination one two one two three times in a row and catching him with an uppercut and and or using his boxing skills
With one hand to to outmaneuver an outboxer aggressive pressure fighter like eastside pit bull cruz
He's fought a different variety fighters longer fighters
shorter fighters got smaller than him guys bigger than him
um
Just just has shown a high level of IQ and an ability to fight
Anywhere that you want him to fight whether it's back foot or front foot now
These reasons on top of the style that chicory stevensson brings to the table
Is why I would favor tank davis in the fight chicory stevensson is a defensive fighter
That tries to use his counter punching ability, but he's a defensive fighter from the waist up only he doesn't use a lot of foot movement
So he likes to fight in the pocket. He's not a a lateral mover in the way that a devon haney is his feet
Aren't nearly as good. He's good at taking a hop step back
Half step back half steps in the distance, but he's going to be right there
He can't he relies on barely making you miss and being in position to make you to make you pay
You know what i'm saying? And so with a godlike tank davis. Yeah, you can probably barely make
Somebody like osco valdez miss. Yeah, it's a little easier to make somebody that's 35 years old
Like jamael heron barely make him miss or it might be easier to make somebody like rosson concecial
Barely miss but when you fight in the style that chicory stevensson fights in
The margin for error is so small because if you misjudge that distance by half an inch
If you misjudge that distance by a centimeter now you caught on the chin and he's used to punches just
Barely going by his face face where his tank. This is not disputed
This is something that we that i don't think anyone will argue tank will be have better handspede than anyone chicory has ever fought
He will hit harder than anyone chicory has ever fought
He will have better timing than anyone chicory has ever fought and he is more athletic than anyone chicory
Um has ever fought and so when you look at this fight
It's going to be in the pocket and you have one fighter in chicory stevensson
That has to out point tank to win and he has to do it without ever getting hurt to where tank can get back in the fight
Oh, you getting you get knocked down now. It's a 10-8 round. He has the smaller margin for error
He could be winning a fight
And tank catching with the wrong shot and now the fight is over tank davis
Will win this fight because of all of these reasons, but he also has a larger margin for error
He can be down on the scorecards and still win a fight
He can be down seven rounds to four going into the last round
He can be down eight rounds to three going into the last round and it won't matter because that whole time
He is dangerous from round one to round 12 whereas your core stevensson
He has had problems getting guys that are small that don't have the chin that tank davis has
He has had problems getting those guys out of there
Guys like robson kaseksiya where he was boom full steam ahead going for the knockout. It was very very difficult for him
And he was fighting in a style that tank davis would eat a lot
If he tried to fight tank davis like that and then the other key point is that tank davis
Is someone who is very cerebral in the ring. He don't just go out there walk you down throw a thousand punches
And knock you out. He thinks he sees what you're doing
And if I with my eye see that's your core stevensson his defense with his hips when you're throwing straight shots at him
He likes to pull straight back and barely make you miss if you're trying to come over the top on him
He's going dip down to his left try to duck up underneath your punches
That's how he gets out of the way of people over and over again off the strength of his reflexes have been better
Than everyone he's ever been in the ring with his reflexes will not be better than tank davis
And you cannot go in the ring with your vante tank davis and do the same shit over and over and over again
And think that he's not going to pick up on it
He will pick up on it
He will end up catching Shakur
Whether it be a straight left
But more importantly probably be a right hook because they're both going to be in a closed stance
Is they're both southpaws and so I can see Shakur running into a right hook from javante tank davis
Whether it be to the body or up or up top and then the other factor is that tank davis is a highly underrated defensive fighter
He's a highly underrated defensive fighter. So his defense is still top 15 when you look at his connect against percentage
It's still top 15 in the entire sport of boxing and he's one of the most powerful punches
And he's one of the best finishers and he's one of the most accurate punchers in the sport of boxing
So he has all of that going for him and on top of all of that Shakur won't be able to get away from him
And Shakur doesn't have the power to walk him down
So they will be either be a in the pocket in the center of the ring or it'll be tank davis
The one moving forward and guys are not able to move to to fight tank davis going backwards
The only people that you look that has some success against tank you look at mario barriere's maybe early in the fight
you look at somebody like um
Isak pitbull cruise into parts of that fight and then you look at roly-rimiro in certain parts of that fight
It was guys that were strong. They were able to push him back. They were able to make him fight off the back foot
And even they started getting countered and got their ass beat. So Shakur steveson doesn't have that style
He abandoned his jab the last fight
He he didn't have good transitions if you go look at him
He was making cassay see how miss but he was not making them pay
He was not firing off those counters fast enough and if you make tank miss one
It's another one coming just as fast right back at it with a third behind that one
So that defensive style of just having good defense and alluding the guy hoping that he stopped punching tank
Will not stop on Shakur if he gets Shakur compromised
He is going to work work him over bro. And so tank davis has showed us to the last point
He's knocked out everyone that or put down everyone that is taller than him and Shakur is taller than him
The one guy that he didn't stop was um was isak pitbull cruise who's five foot two and tank was punching down
The other guy that he didn't stop was years ago. It was a six round fight
He was one inch taller than tank but tank did put him down twice in that fight and had the fight been an eight
Round or a ten rounder. He clearly had to do hurting the sixth round
It just wasn't a long enough fight, but he did put that down put that dude down twice
So everyone that he's been in the ring with that has been taller than him
He has either stopped them or put them down multiple times
So he will be punching up at Shakur, which is what he's used to which will make him a much more dynamic puncher
Than he was and say the east side pitbull cruise fight
So tank over Shakur because of his counter punching ability the accuracy of his punches his
Explosiveness and his power and because Shakur has such a slim margin for error
You got Shakur that has to be perfect for 12 rounds to escape with a victory for what tank
Tank only has to be perfect for one second of a round and the fight is over and on top of that
He has just as good boxing skills when you look at his ring IQ
You look at his accuracy you look at his defense and you look at how he
Transitions his defense to offense when you look at all those things you got to say the tank Davis can box just as well
If not better than Shakur Stevenson on top of having that it factor of being able to end the fight at any moment
With one punch and that's my that's my third round
All right
Okay, yeah tremendous. Well, but okay, let's go JC baby go ahead shoot your shot. All right, so Shakur wins this fight
In boxing we we see boxer versus puncher you always take you generally always take the boxer over the puncher, right?
And it's a couple things
reasons why I feel like Shakur wins this fight
A is his distance control he controls distance very well when he's not trying to get too greedy and go and fight
um his positioning so it's not so much with um Shakur it's not so much about
His foot speed and being of step around and create angles. It's about his foot positioning his body position him being in position to be able to
See and that's the last thing. He's his eyes. He sees everything that's coming, right? So
There's not going to be a shot that tank David Strowes that Shakur does not see coming because when you look at his last
uh since the noctilia fight
Uh, which would be Jamel herring osco Valdez Robinson cassay sial
He's landed a career high and in punches landing each one of those fights 164 against herring. He stopped him in the 11th round
189 against osco Valdez stayed in the pocket
189 against Valdez and did 199 against cassay sial. So
One would think like oh, okay. He's in the pocket more. So he's getting hit more. No, according to compi box
Jamel herring 87 punches landed uh through through 11 rounds when he got stopped
Valdez 110 through 12
cassay sial caught in the compi box 60 punches 60 punches landed um through 12 rounds
So what he does is he positions himself to make you miss and make you pay on the other end
But now what we're seeing in him is a more offensive style where he is coming forward, right?
He wasn't on the back foot against Jamel here Jamel herring was a bigger guy
In fact, we if you go back to that fight you listen to bow Mack tell
Jamel herring to put his side to use his size against Shakur because he is the bigger guy
What happened? Shakur still stepped forward and got it
He wasn't dancing around the ring with Valdez. He put the offense on Valdez and still didn't get hit. So that's 20
20% against herring 20 connect percentage total against herring 21% against uh
Valdez and then 12% against cassay sial and knows all fights in which he stayed
In the pocket he positions himself in a way to where he can if he wants to be offensive
He can get his offense off where he can still see what you're coming back with and that's where Shakur
Wins the fight we we often say oh
You got to be perfect for 12 rounds. You got to be perfect for 12 rounds
It's not like we haven't seen a high IQ boxer just be perfect for 12 rounds in Devin Haney
Now now that wasn't against a tank davis
However, it's not to say that he cannot be perfect because we've seen him put on master classes in the ring
That's what he does. He rises to the occasion of the opponent that's standing across from him
That's what he has. He has that dog in the and and he's going to
Unless you can convince me that
Tame Davis is going to throw a shot that Shakur Stevenson does not see coming
I don't think he wins this fight. I don't
I don't think he gets hit with a lot of jabs and well and and the thing is he's not going to be
sitting back waiting for tank. It's not going to be
a um
Later stage Floyd may whether where I'm just waiting for you and you come no
He's going to come to tank babies. He is going to take him
He's going to put the offense and he's going to control the distance
But the way he positions himself to be able to hit
And not hit when you throw to not get hit and then hit
That is what that that's what's when that is what will win the fight for Shakur Stevenson. I rest
All right, you got six minutes left. All right, you rest
All right, okay
I got you um
so
He started off phrasing this as a boxer versus a puncher and that's not true
It's a boxer versus a boxer puncher like tank. Davis is not just
a puncher like
Egbert Langer if you want to bring up a puncher Egbert Langer is just a puncher and we don't even know if he can do that no more
Tank Davis is a boxer puncher like he there's ain't no boxer versus a puncher matchup
So that's one rebuttal right there like tank. Davis can box his ass off
There is a reason that every time you hear Shakur Stevenson talk about tank Davis
He says tank davis versus me that is the super fight in the future
Not because he respects tanks power but because he respects his skills
So this is not a boxer versus puncher matchup. This is a boxer versus a boxer puncher now the distance control point
J-Tess now brings up a point and I understand Shakur Stevenson has had good distance control to this point in his career
well
A lot of guys were able to do things successfully
Up and until the point that they fought Javante tank Davis up until he fought Javante tank Davis
Leo Santa Cruz his style of being a volume puncher being someone that is able to overwhelm you
That shit worked for him with every person he had ever been in the ring with because he had a vengeance only other loss
It got his ass knocked out in six rounds against tank Davis
My brother um my brother Jose Pedroza before fighting tank Davis his style of being herky jerky
Switching stances doing all this extra shit yelling in the ring
All that shit that he used to do it worked up until the point that he fought Javante tank Davis
So don't give me what Shakur Stevenson did against Oscar Valdez
Don't give me what Shakur Stevenson did against Jamel Henry or what he did against Nakathila
It's some sort of microcosm as to how that's going to translate the tank Davis because they ain't tank and tank ain't them
We can't argue that tank is more explosive than all of them
We can't argue that tank is a better boxer than all of them
We can't argue that tank is more athletic than all of them
He checks all the boxes far more than all of those fighters that you mentioned trying to make the point that
Shakur Stevenson is going to somehow control distance with tank Davis the way that he controlled distance against those fighters
You also made in your argument that Shakur is going to be walking to tank that Shakur is now fighting more
Offensively and letting his hands go more when you let your hands go more and you fighting a more offensive style
That leaves you open more to counter punches that leaves you open more to exchanges
So as a result him fighting in this new style trying to walk to somebody who has more knockouts than he has fights
Okay, you're gonna walk to that guy. Good luck with that walking to him trying to be more offensive
It's going to leave him open more and tank Davis has proven. Oh, I see you Mario Barrios
You are trying to jab me. You're trying to keep distance. So I am going to par your jab away
I'm gonna par your jab make your jab nonexistent and I'm firing a left hand down the line against you
So do you not think that he is going to see oh Shakur?
Oh Shakur you trying to barely make me miss by pulling back every time I throw my left hand
So I'm going to use my friends. I will fake my left hand make you lean back and it's a far as right hook coming right behind it
Tank Davis will see the tendencies and he will see the the moves that Shakur makes far better than anyone that Shakur
has ever been in the ring with bro
so
Miss me with the comparisons of people don't connect against Shakur
People people do this. That's because he's never fought anyone as good as tank
You got Shakur got the lowest connect against percentage. You got tank Davis got the second highest connect percentage
Something has to give in this fight. Excuse me, but until someone
Goes 36 minutes without being touched by tank Davis
I am going to say that he is going to touch Shakur Stevenson because
Oscar Valdez had minimal success. It ain't like like when you said they names and shit you said somebody landed 80
I heard that someone else landed a hundred and something
Like I did hear that I didn't hear like yo, they landed zero punches against Shakur
I didn't hear yo they landed five punches against Shakur. Somebody landed 80
somebody landed a hundred and something but yes somehow
He couldn't control the distance a hundred percent of the time against them
But he's gonna control distance and he's gonna be perfect against tank Davis
Hey, oh no, what's going to happen in this fight is that it's going to be an even boxing match
They're going to be even up until the point Shakur Stevenson miscalculates tank Davis's explosiveness
He miscalculates how quickly tank Davis can close distance with a shot and then tank Davis catches his ass with some hot
Shit hurts him and we all know that the ozio ass recovering from tank Davis
is three percent
I'm out
All right at three percent comment don't count. It was after the bed
Let's just don't count this shit don't count
All right JC, baby. Come on
Give me what you got
Well, I mean, okay
So a lot of the same things that k.o said in his rebuttal round goes the opposite direction you you spoke about in your round that um
Tank Davis is top 15 and connect against percentage
again
Not a fighter
With the talent of Shakur on the other side of him
He's tops and connect percentage you just said and your rebuttal round
again, not a fighter
On the level of Shakur not a has any okay
Tell me this is any of those fighters that uh that tank Davis is is number one and connect percentage against are any of those guys in the top
100 and connect against uh percentage. No, not right. So so they so they're guys that are there to be hit
Shakur Stevenson's not going to be there to be hit. That's what it is
Like you can say just as easily as you can say
um
That he he he can keep distance on guys that are not tank Davis
It goes the same way because he hasn't been in the ring with anybody with this with the positioning with the eyes
I keep going back to the eyes because as long as I can see everything coming
Even if you hit me with it, I can roll with it. I can pull with it a little bit
I can do things to where that power does not hit me and I'm going a lot of the guys that he fight
And they stand that boom they walking in the shots. They don't have time to brace. Why because they don't see him coming
He's positioning himself to where he can see every shot coming and despite what you say
Even if tank lands 110 punty 120 punty whatever he does because Shakur can see
Everything coming when it's strong before it's strong. He knows what's getting ready to happen. Guess what now?
I can prepare for that. I can prepare myself the shot that hurts you in boxing is a shot that you don't see coming
There won't be a a punching this fight
That Shakur won't see coming
And I rest my rebuttal man
Oh, we man five five three rounds, baby. Wow man. Tell me what you think dub right side
So man in this round, uh
And I
Go to be up man. Come back to me on this
No
I
Go through my points. I gotta see cuz I thought this was a close round. I go through them while I talk about
Hey, why hey why he doing that everybody puts him hand clapping mode using some thumbs up in the chat for me and my brother
J chestnut man. Yeah, I put some
Put some hand clapping mode is in the chat for my brother, bro. Go ahead right
Man, so in this third round man, um, kale. He came out talking about, um, how tanky to set back your puncher
He talked about the counterpunching ability how he would faint and that would be one of the ways he would be able to land
I believe he said the right hook
He could paint the left hand to land that right hook. He talked about the
Variation the variety of different fighters how tank has fought a better variety than uh, Shakur has
He talked about the lack of Shakur's footwork and how
Uh, um, also he talked about how nobody Shakur's fault has the hand speed the power to time and athleticism
of tank Davis
um
He talked about how tank has a larger margin
Uh for error they should course you go we have to fight fight and how the fire is probably gonna take
In the pocket and because it's taking place in the pocket is gonna give that opportunity to land his power
um, he talked about how uh tank is is a
A tanky man in the ring and how uh Shakur is straight back going to again
Failing and and throwing their right hand. Um, you talked about um tank is defense
Or how is is um one of the top defensive
Fighters one of the most powerful fighters and one of the most accurate punches
Um, he said, you know can or you can't beat tank with defense of long with with defense alone
You're gonna have to land punches on them
Um, um
Everybody talked in them and uh how uh Shakur has to be perfect for 12
Right and think only has to be perfect for one second to uh end the fight
My brother j chestnut then he came in he talked about how uh, this was a boxer versus a puncher usually
Uh fans like myself choose the punch. I mean, excuse me the boxer over the puncher
Um, he talked about Shakur's distance control how it's not necessarily about Shakur's foot speed
But it's more about his foot positioning. Uh, he talked about and one of the things I really liked that he brought up
Was how uh Shakur sees everything that's going to be coming and so, uh, he's going to be able to roll with those shots
Take some of the pop off of them
Excuse me. He talked about how he's gonna try to make you miss and pay or yeah make you miss and then make you pay
Um, he talked about how Shakur isn't just a back foot fighter in his previous or in his latest fights
He's shown much more offense and coming forward in the fight. He talked about how he he gets hit very little in the pocket
Um, then he also he brought up how uh, if debon can be perfect
he uh, uh
Shakur and two the problem I had with that was was you sat there and said although it wasn't tank don't say that
You're not saying that when you bring it up, but um
Yeah, so that that was more or less that round going to the rebuttals
I thought one of the the smart things k.l brought up
I think he is a puncher, but he's a boxer puncher. You know what I'm saying? He's not just a puncher. Uh, I definitely agree with it
um
he talked about how, um
What worked against other fighters
For Shakur probably ain't gonna be able to work against tank then he went back and brought up once again a hand speed the power of timing
the athleticism how
he has more than any of the other fighters that um
That uh, uh, uh Shakur has fought
Uh, Jay, he came back man and he he said hey same thing with uh tank
The lesser or or he's had success against lesser competition than Shakur
And how the the power from Shakur would not be the same
Um because Shakur is gonna see those punches coming
Man, it was a tough round for me in this one. I gave it a knockout
I gotta say two things once again, Jay
Use your time brother use your time. I wish you would have used all your time
Or or used it better than you did also. I think um
Once again when you kind of discredit yourself when you say certain things like although it wasn't against
I would I would say next time just say that hey, um
This is this is this person was able to do it. Hey, Shakur is just as good of a boxer. Why he can't do it
You know what I'm saying? I gave it a round of knockout though. All right. All right. Oh the smoke. What's the smoke?
What you got, baby?
Um, yeah, I got um, I got a clean sweep
uh from for knockout um
and ultimately it was the uh, it was the rebuttal the um
You know the attributes of Shakur playing into the strengths of uh tank that did it for me
The uh, they you know, both of them, you know
They're respective
Competition being awash you can't really you know, you can't really project what they're gonna do against each other based on their past
Previous opponents. I agree with that part. But yeah, but the way that you're describing how
um, Shakur was going to what Shakur did well and how he was going to uh the beat tank that actually
Is kind of plays right into tanks hands. So yeah
knockout
All right. All right. All right. We come about the grade digger. We talk about the grade y'all what you got B
FTP baby. What's that?
First off
Mahomi JC, I don't I don't know you Brody. Um, I respect you
That was your best round
Absolutely your best round. That was the round. Um that you made me you made me think. Um
Because I will man, I that was that was a good round. It was a very good round
I appreciate the the the direction that you went. I appreciate um, I appreciate what you did
um, but I think
The the only flaw that and I was leaning towards you, you know, and KO is my guy. That's that's my brother
I was leaning towards you. Um, and I'm like, okay, this is he got him JC got him and then you didn't you didn't um,
You didn't go at that one piece. Um that KO said when KO said
Um
Shakur is going to get hit
right
You you beautifully came back and said Shakur sees
Everything he sees it. Um, and you said the one that you don't see is the one that hurts you
That's what you said. That was that was masterful. I give you super respect for that for that point
Like I see the nuances in things. I don't be looking at the whole I'm looking at the
Because everybody knows this point, right? So there's nuances in there that's going to sway this way or sway it that way
Um, where I was where I wanted you to go that you didn't go is you didn't go farther into
KO saying he's going to get hit
like
What happens then you know saying so like when KO said like this man doesn't have fights where he is
Only got hit five times or only got hit this you you sort of helped him when you said he seized the punch. All right, well
Leo santa Cruz saw the uppercut coming. He was looking right at it
There's several fighters. They saw tank landing shots
They was the outcome still happens. That's what I was. I wanted you to do if you to went there, bro
You would have got I'm not even gonna lie. You would have got me. Um, this was a very close round for me
But I got a sway to KO specifically for that point nothing more
Nonetheless just that one point you was man. I was rocking with you
And I'm let you know sometimes I want everybody to know bro. I picked tank to annihilate Shakur
No, I heard you say it the other day. No, I heard it but my but you you literally had me
You had me like
Thinking when you were saying your points that that was beautifully done. I give you mad
Mad respect for that one. I gotta I gotta give it to kio because I wanted you to
To go in a little bit more on that one. Well, you didn't do that. You you gave it to kio on that
But salute to you k
All right. All right, man
I debate man
Congratulations to uh, hello. Hello debate. Yes, sir and jay
Yeah, man
I would say for me the first round was the best one for me if you just said something like uh, just told me how
Shakur is gonna be there you went the to loma route
For stardom and you didn't mention oscar delahoya and floy mayweather
I didn't know how you leave that out of the the top ranked stars that have been made top like stars been made
Oh, okay. I got you. I got you. I was man. I don't even know how that was just like wow. Anyway, but that was my favorite round for you
For 20 years to go smoke. Hey, hey, you've been doing that shit for a long time
That's what I'm saying
About 20 years ago we got them all the party
Yeah, I'm saying you went to you went further back than that you went to fucking you went to iron mike tyson you went
Fucking Larry Holmes like
I guess y'all did so I guess y'all y'all y'all had already gave me the round when I say floy mayweather many pack y'all y'all didn't hear that
That's the second round you said that one. No, anyway, I'll talk about the first one. Anyway, I got
You guys
I got a rapid bro. Let's get everybody last words. I know be a busy. So let's get you
Also, I loved your energy man. J chestnut love the energy bro
Love the perspective
Let them know where to find you man. What you got going on
Everybody know where I'm at bro. I don't even gotta go. They know everybody listening know who I am and they know where it's at
You can act like you don't know where it's at. I just want to give my brother j chestnut respect. Well, I don't know where you're at
I need to know where I like I like this brother dog. I like him
I you know on your shit. He just debate just straight debate, bro
We took an L. We took an L and it's what it is. Oh, I
I respect that more than anything bro like because for me like I'm gonna tell y'all straight up, bro
I know ko undefeated this nigga right here with two thumbs is
Unfucking defeated. All right. So
Hey, we'll have that we'll have that we'll have that but I fuck with j bro
I like this brother, bro
So I want to know who you at so I can subscribe and I can follow you. I like I like this
That that's all I you gonna hear right now be a bro. I appreciate you as always man. Keep doing your thing
All right, peace man. All right, j let everybody know what you got going on everybody
We need to force j to start a goddamn channel. I know you got
Yeah, bro, j gotta start a channel around this big j let everybody know what you got going on man
Or y'all know j j about the smoking shit. So j might call one of y'all ass out because he
J don't j don't duck knows more. He might call one of y'all ass out. So y'all better listen carefully j go go ahead and give you
your last words
Nah, man, so so uh to your point man me otb was talking earlier man. So I do have a channel. I just don't be uh
consistently um
putting putting uh content out there, you know what I'm saying? So I'm gonna try to start a little bit. I'm gonna see what my schedule look like
Tomorrow and I'm gonna drop a few videos. It's called the pound for pound sports line
Yeah, so we talk everything. We don't talk just boxing. We talk football. So this weekend. I'm looking to preview uh,
Dallas Philly, um, and I want to do the breakdown of uh
Buffalo Kansas City from my perspective and then I'll um
Do a video doing all my picks for this week as well as all my picks against the spread this week too because I like to do that
If you pick Philly
If you pick Philly, I don't I actually didn't I never had a school. I never come back
I do got Dallas winning that game this Sunday, but
All right, cool. Yeah
Yeah, oh and shout out shout out to laury re with the 25 dollars in the cash app. I appreciate you laury
Thanks. Well, thanks for showing a little bit. Jay man. Great. Great. Um, great debate. I told you what I was gonna do to you though, bro
Hey, man, I appreciate the love man. It ain't you know, you know, I'm saying ain't no hard feelings, man
You know, like I say man legacy matters about who you get in the ring with you feel me
So you take some else when you fight the best when the best fight the best
That's what you do. Do you have any do you have any debate anybody that you're calling out in the future?
Or do we need to
I can't get it off my mind, bro. I don't feel like I got a fair shake against coach, bro
I swear, but I still
I
See me see me a couple of see me a couple of topics and I'll get it coaching. We'll
I can tell you now. Bivall is his guy. So if he thinks Bivall can be either Zerto or better be of their highlight
Because he was early on the he was early on the Bivall train. So if he thinks Bivall can be either one of those guys
I'm with it. Let's set it up. All right, bro. That's a bit. I appreciate you coming over. Yeah, sir. Thank you, bro
All righty. Hey, uh, best dad ever. I'm gonna take your goddamn wrench
I've been take your wrench get out of here with that Philly talk the only one that can talk about Philly is
is bf and bumpy
Bumpy can talk about Philly and bf can talk about Philly anybody else mentioning Philly
Get out of here, bro. We ain't walking with no damn shegels the seagulls
None of anything bro. Let me go to smoke smoke
Well, what up? You can find me get this smoke. Uh, yeah, we talked about boxing just started doing content
You know two a couple weeks ago. Um, yeah, we take the morning shift right now
I'll be uploading some videos so we can chop up to find the points of stuff soon enough
But yeah, come check us out and live if you're you know on your morning on your morning commute
Whatever chop it up
Always love always a nice time chop it up over here. Uh, knock out kq kc finally on the panel with you, man
I've been listening you do your thing for uh for a minute now
Uh, yeah, man, I'm over here smiling there and my camera's not on but I'm sure you can hear the smile of voice
Left right side already a piece of that toxic ass chat you got fucking knock out
I don't know what the fuck wrong with people. They need a hug and goddamn jesus. He did. He did. He did. He did man.
Hey, hold on.
Smoke has a chance smoke is going to be going for his first w next week smoke
You want to tell him about your debate next week? Oh, no, man. I like to be I like to be uh,
Immanuel Burton of this bitch like I'm gonna let you guys keep robbing me and keep talking and shit
And just I'm gonna go down in history like that like the baddest man that came with w for fucking whatever reason
I
Smoke has a debate next Thursday night same time a 30 after I do my picks
It's gonna be him versus q the guy from the lost order box in the lab
They doing Devin Haney and she cool stevens and that's gonna be a good one, man
So I can't I can't wait to hear them brothers go into the smoke. I appreciate you as always man
Hey smoke represent now represent for death. Yeah, yeah, man. Q your shit
Right. Yeah. Yeah, I see what you gotta do now. You like a little bit of civil war happening. I get you
Here we go. Have some fun with that one though. Please. I already brought. I appreciate you man. I'll highlight you
KQ KC the singing old G. Yes, sir. I know you're following the fights this weekend
I know you're going a lot more. He go live eight days a week and it's only seven days
And man is live every damn day
Yeah, don't stop man appreciate you coming up man. Let everybody know what you got going on and where to find you and all that good
This stuff. Yes, sir. Of course, we're gonna be live tomorrow 11 o'clock a
m and of course I will be calling all the fights Saturday and
Hope you can join me and of course find me me and knock out Boston right here
at nine o'clock
Sunday morning nine o'clock a m central time and yeah, I'm gonna be on time sunday
Because we got so much to talk about you. I know how many fights it is the weekend. We got so much to talk about
See, I better come to in show
I will be having an interview with the young kid offer
Okay, it's not eight eleven. He won't get in there to 12 o'clock
Okay, he won't get in there to 12
But we're still gonna start at 11 because I still got a lot to talk about all right
So come on in and uh, and that's about it man. All right
Peace out baby. All right. All right. Peace out. Thank you. All right. I'm out of here
Hey, I was reading a comment
Jenelle
Hey, Anthony Parker
That's cap
That man you mentioned I ain't gonna say his name he posted he called me out for a debate never showed up never gave no times or nothing
So it should sound good
That should sound good, but uh
He know where to find me know where to find everybody
Hey, bro, like he's more than welcome if that if smoke is what he want
I set the shit up and we can get it popping with it. Ain't nobody ducking. No, nobody on no boxing talk shit, but don't don't do that
Don't do that, bro. Go ahead right side
Talk yo shit
hell of a debate
Fantast man salute the uk o great victory tonight man salute my brother jay chest night
He's a regardless of him losing the night man. He always come with the smoke and uh, man
I got a lot of respect for the brother a lot of respect shout out the kqk seat in a hell of a moderator
Bf and then smoke along with myself judging man. I thought man. It was a hell of a show
I appreciate you always allow me out with you. Um, I know what we doing over at right side, man
Rocking with the right side. We've been having some hell of an interviews with damn the family man
That's what we call everybody who come on the show man. It's the family over there
So y'all make sure y'all take it out. Uh, and man, k. Yo always appreciate you bruh always appreciate you
I read it man. Appreciate you coming through y'all take it easy
Yes, sir
All right, man. Look man. Appreciate everybody coming through. We got another w man 3o
You know what i'm saying? Did I think we came we saw we conquered and we still got an open invitation anybody that
Won't smoke man and don't forget we got the debate next week man. We got my brothers get the smoke
Versus cute guy from the lost order boxing they going at it on different hanging issue
Of course thieves and that's gonna be a great one. Um and watch boxing this weekend man
Rewinding the show to check out my picks. We got a real good record on the picks
I'm putting it online because we picking some upsets this week. We're gonna see if we can rank supreme get a couple of upsets
Get a couple of big bags, man. We'll see what's popping this weekend
Besides everybody came through showed up and showed out bftb boxing dub right side get the smoke j chestnut
Um kq kc boxing network all those brothers up on the panel y'all go subscribe to their channel go check them out
And do um and go check out that content man
They're doing great work again shout out to bf shout out to my beautiful wife miss knockout bumpy thompson zulu lion
Anthony parker jj same fight different round. Um best dad ever lory reed zulu lion. I be who I be eric o
Let me see who else we had bumpy thompson in the building. We're those love mr. Sheldon
Don't sell miss Sheldon you slid through the back door. I ain't even see you bro salute leon robson king d white fight fan white fight fan
No one beats dev already. Um, let me see here. Johnny Q was in the building everybody that showed them showed out man
I appreciate every each and every one of y'all got a green. I see you dominant
I see you shout out to everybody man subscribe to the channel if you new here share the share the live stream
Let everybody know what we're doing. Um over here and if you want some smoke
If you want some smoke, you understand what I'm saying knock out box of 80 60 yahoo.com is the email if you want it with me
You want to be one of my brothers or just anything you want to judge you want to you want to be a moderator
We are open to everyone participating. Just know
That seat is hot
That seat is real real real real real hot
And we talked that boxing over here, so you better come with it, but I appreciate y'all enjoy the rest of y'all night and with that
We out of here. Peace out y'all
Ciao